2010-06-04 18:31:57,"Please ignore prior tweets, as that was someone pretending to be Elon Musk :) This is actually me.",en,92,17,1,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2011-12-28 22:27:08,So true :),en,20,4,1,[],pos,pos
2011-12-27 23:38:55,If you ever wanted to know the *real* truth about the moon landings ...(best Onion article ever),en,118,18,1,"[['Onion', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2011-12-26 16:29:50,Walked around a neighborhood recently rebuilt with help from APJ and others,en,97,13,1,"[['APJ', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2011-12-26 16:23:04,"It was Xmas, so we brought presents for the kids at the orphanage. the kids at the orphanage don't usually get much.",en,117,19,3,"[['X', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2011-12-26 15:45:18,"Met with UNICEF, Doctors Without Borders and Artists for Peace & Justice. Elon Musk support UNICEF, Doctors Without Borders and Artists for Peace & Justice and would recommend others do too.",en,123,21,2,"[['UNICEF', 'I-ORG'], ['Doctors', 'I-ORG'], ['Without', 'I-ORG'], ['Borders', 'I-ORG'], ['Artists', 'I-ORG'], ['for', 'I-ORG'], ['Peace', 'I-ORG'], ['&', 'I-ORG'], ['Justice', 'I-ORG'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['UNICEF', 'I-ORG'], ['Doctors', 'I-ORG'], ['Without', 'I-ORG'], ['Borders', 'I-ORG'], ['Artists', 'I-ORG'], ['for', 'I-ORG'], ['Peace', 'I-ORG'], ['&', 'I-ORG'], ['Justice', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2011-12-26 15:23:40,Just returned from a trip to Haiti. Covered a lot of ground and saw many tough situations. They need a lot of help.,en,115,23,3,"[['Haiti', 'I-LOC']]",neg,pos
2011-12-26 15:05:19,Single character Tweets are the ulitmate extension of the Twitmeme...,en,69,10,1,"[['Ttme', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neu
2011-12-26 04:06:06,I,und,1,1,1,[],pos,neu
2011-12-24 01:41:33,The Russians are having some challenges with The Russians's rockets. Too many of the engineers that designed their rockets have retired:,en,140,20,2,"[['Russians', 'I-MISC'], ['Russians', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2011-12-24 01:33:35,We had a long and interesting conversation on many subjects. He has exciting ideas for extending He's creative talents beyond music.,en,131,21,2,"[['He', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2011-12-24 01:29:19,Kanye stopped by the SpaceX rocket factory today.,en,71,9,2,"[['Kanye', 'I-PER'], ['SpaceX', 'I-ORG']]",neg,neg
2011-12-22 11:30:10,Model S options are out! Performance in red and black for me. Elon Musk will deliver me's car in June/July.,en,120,20,4,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,neu
2011-12-22 09:46:16,"Hi, I'm Art Garfunkel. Have you heard the sound of silence? Because, you know, the sound of silence makes a sound...",en,120,19,3,"[['Art', 'I-PER'], ['Garfunkel', 'I-PER']]",neg,neu
2011-12-22 03:12:52,Raul Campos invited Elon Musk to do a guest DJ gig on KCRW. Hear my random holiday season music selections at,en,125,21,2,"[['Raul', 'I-PER'], ['Campos', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['KCRW', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2011-12-21 23:17:11,Yum! Even better than deep fried butter:,en,62,8,2,[],pos,pos
2011-12-21 11:13:59,"Yeah, this really is me, as me's Mom will attest. Not sure me can handle just doing 140 char missives. Will put longer thoughts on G+",en,140,27,3,[],pos,pos
2011-12-21 11:00:19,"Got called randomly by Kanye West today and received a download of Kanye West's thoughts, ranging from shoes to Moses. Kanye West was polite, but opaque.",en,136,24,2,"[['Kanye', 'I-PER'], ['West', 'I-PER'], ['Kanye', 'I-PER'], ['West', 'I-PER'], ['Moses', 'I-PER'], ['Kanye', 'I-PER'], ['West', 'I-PER']]",neg,neu
2011-12-21 10:48:29,His singing and acting talent will be sorely missed: South Park sequel coming soon...,en,108,15,1,"[['South', 'I-MISC'], ['Park', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2011-12-21 10:42:52,Why does the crowd cry over the glorious leader Kim Il Sung's death? Fear of being shot may play a role:,en,128,22,2,"[['Kim', 'I-PER'], ['Il', 'I-PER'], ['Sung', 'I-PER']]",pos,neg
2011-12-21 10:30:05,Sam Harris also wrote a nice piece on the awesomeness of Hitchens: May the good man RIP.,en,110,18,1,"[['Sam', 'I-PER'], ['Harris', 'I-PER'], ['Hitchens', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2011-12-21 10:26:51,"Read ""Lying"", the new book by my friend Sam Harris. Excellent cover art and lots of good reasons not to lie!",en,109,21,2,"[['Lying', 'I-MISC'], ['Sam', 'I-PER'], ['Harris', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2011-12-04 03:33:52,Am reading a great biography of Ben Franklin by Isaacson. Highly recommended.,en,77,12,2,"[['Ben', 'I-PER'], ['Franklin', 'I-PER'], ['Isaacson', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2011-12-03 08:22:07,That was a total non sequitur btw,en,33,7,1,[],neg,neu
2011-12-03 08:20:28,"Great Voltaire quote, arguably better than Twain. Hearing news of Voltaire's own death, Voltaire replied news of his own death were true, only premature.",en,136,21,2,"[['Voltaire', 'I-PER'], ['Twain', 'I-PER'], ['Voltaire', 'I-PER'], ['Voltaire', 'I-PER']]",pos,neu
2011-12-01 10:29:04,I made the volume on the Model S go to 11. Now Elon Musk just need to work in a miniature Stonehenge...,en,118,22,2,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Stonehenge', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2011-12-01 09:55:11,"Went to Iceland on Sat to ride bumper cars on ice! No, not the country, Vlad's rink in Van Nuys. Awesome family fun :)",en,141,25,3,"[['Iceland', 'I-LOC'], ['Sa', 'I-MISC'], ['Vlad', 'I-PER'], ['Van', 'I-LOC'], ['Nuys', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-12-25 22:37:56,Interesting premise. Elon Musk will read it.,en,51,7,2,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-12-25 22:02:34,V cute! Merry Xmas.,en,35,5,2,[],pos,pos
2012-12-24 02:44:12,Cowboy riding the rocket no problemo,en,58,7,1,[],pos,neg
2012-12-24 02:32:20,Single camera view of the 40 meter rocket hover,en,69,10,1,[],pos,neu
2012-12-24 02:20:49,Then we took him for a ride: 40 meter hover flight vid of the SpaceX Grasshopper test rocket,en,114,19,1,"[['SpaceX', 'I-MISC'], ['Grasshopper', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-12-24 02:12:11,"To provide a little perspective on the size of Grasshopper, we added a 6 ft cowboy to the rocket",en,118,20,1,"[['Grasshopper', 'I-PER']]",pos,neu
2012-12-19 23:29:54,Very much agree with this great review of Chasing Ice on Ars Technica,en,91,14,1,"[['Chasing', 'I-MISC'], ['Ice', 'I-MISC'], ['Ars', 'I-ORG'], ['Technica', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-12-19 01:20:51,"Thanks! “@ev: Have driven a Tesla Model S 50 miles now. a Tesla Model S's clearly the iPhone of cars—by far the best car ever made.""",en,119,23,3,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['iPhone', 'I-MISC'], ['of', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-12-17 18:20:08,A beautiful and awe-inspiring view of Earth from the International Space Station,en,102,13,1,"[['Earth', 'I-LOC'], ['International', 'I-LOC'], ['Space', 'I-LOC'], ['Station', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-12-14 14:49:15,Good piece on volcanoes “@DanRetz: The USGS would seem to disagree.,en,90,12,2,"[['DanR', 'I-ORG'], ['USGS', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-12-14 14:44:20,Roughly equivalent to a 747 flight from LA to London (one way).,en,73,13,1,"[['LA', 'I-LOC'], ['London', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neu
2012-12-14 14:42:47,That's why I'm a believer in solar power. We have a giant fusion reactor conveniently located in the sky.,en,121,20,2,[],pos,neu
2012-12-14 14:21:17,"Exactly MT ""@DanRetz IMHO: continuing the uncontrolled experiment of adding co2 to atmosphere is a bad idea.”",en,109,17,1,"[['DanRz', 'I-ORG'], ['IM', 'I-ORG']]",neg,neg
2012-12-14 13:57:53,It is hard to argue with a thermometer. Global warming is real and accelerating. Wish Global warming wasn't.,en,118,18,4,"[['Global', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-12-12 20:06:11,Cool video recap of the big events of the year by Google #Zeitgeist2012,en,93,14,1,"[['Google', 'I-ORG'], ['Zeitge', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-12-12 17:44:27,"Relative to kerosene, methane is not prone to coking, but we would run v high purity anyway for max Isp.",en,114,21,1,[],pos,neu
2012-12-12 17:40:48,"Yup or Douglas Aircraft, creator of the awesome DC-3",en,102,12,1,"[['Douglas', 'I-ORG'], ['Aircraft', 'I-ORG'], ['DC', 'I-MISC'], ['-', 'I-MISC'], ['3', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-12-12 17:35:07,"My big worry would be long (hopefully) term when My'm dead, eg v sad situation with once great HP",en,111,20,1,"[['HP', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neg
2012-12-12 17:27:15,"SpaceX will go public at some point, as Elon Musk think SpaceX should ultimately be owned primarily by the public ""@bm_ will SpaceX go public?""",en,131,24,1,"[['SpaceX', 'I-ORG'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['SpaceX', 'I-ORG'], ['SpaceX', 'I-ORG']]",neg,neu
2012-12-12 17:15:02,"Best to study some form of engineering, which is the art of creating useful things that didn't exist before.",en,125,20,1,[],pos,pos
2012-12-12 17:12:05,"Tesla articles 30 mins apart: ""This Stock is Screaming Buy"" and ""This Stock Could Get DESTROYED""",en,140,18,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",neg,neg
2012-12-11 02:54:30,Tesla was just approved for a full Class 1 Massachusetts Auto Sales License by a vote of 4 to 1. Much appreciated!,en,114,22,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['Massachusetts', 'I-MISC'], ['Auto', 'I-MISC'], ['Sales', 'I-MISC'], ['License', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-12-09 23:13:23,"Told my kids (age 8 and 6) that my kids (age 8 and 6) were going to see the Nutcracker, which somehow got translated as the Buttcracker.",en,117,22,1,"[['Nutcracker', 'I-MISC'], ['Buttcracker', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-12-09 08:38:48,Congrats to for being the first to drive a Tesla Model S over 400 miles on a single charge!,en,101,20,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-12-05 05:20:41,Interesting possible answer to the Fermi Paradox,en,71,8,1,"[['Fermi', 'I-MISC'], ['Paradox', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-12-04 04:40:56,Am happy to report that Tesla was narrowly cash flow positive last week. Continued improvement expected through year end.,en,121,19,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-12-02 21:12:03,Uranium ore now available on Amazon! So much more convenient than Uzbekistan #AwesomeXmasGifts,en,116,14,2,"[['Amazon', 'I-ORG'], ['Uzbekistan', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-11-29 10:00:15,Thanks Shervin!,en,24,3,1,"[['Shervin', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-11-28 01:19:37,"Can't put my finger on it, but for some reason the newsstand is looking particularly good right now",en,121,19,1,[],pos,pos
2012-11-27 18:00:03,"But if humanity wishes to become a multi-planet species, then we must figure out how to move millions of people to Mars.",en,120,22,1,"[['Mars', 'I-LOC']]",neg,pos
2012-11-27 17:55:32,"And, yes, Elon Musk do in fact know that this sounds crazy. know is not lost on me. Nor Elon Musk do think SpaceX will do this alone.",en,117,26,3,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['SpaceX', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2012-11-27 17:48:23,"Millions of people needed for Mars colony, so 80k+ would just be the number moving to Mars colony per year",en,121,20,1,"[['Mars', 'I-LOC'], ['Mars', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-11-25 01:53:51,Short vid of the recent mission to the Intl Space Station,en,87,13,1,"[['Intl', 'I-LOC'], ['Space', 'I-LOC'], ['Station', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neu
2012-11-24 00:07:43,SS Heart of Gold powered by the Infinite Improbability Drive!,en,69,11,1,"[['SS', 'I-MISC'], ['Heart', 'I-MISC'], ['of', 'I-MISC'], ['Gold', 'I-MISC'], ['Infinite', 'I-MISC'], ['Imp', 'I-MISC'], ['Drive', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-11-23 19:45:06,My talk for the Royal Aeronautical Society is now online. This gets a little more technical.,en,114,17,3,"[['Royal', 'I-ORG'], ['Aeronautical', 'I-ORG'], ['Society', 'I-ORG']]",neg,neu
2012-11-23 03:16:03,"Liam Neeson's ""Life's Too Short"" sketch is super funny",en,76,10,1,"[['Liam', 'I-PER'], ['Neeson', 'I-PER'], ['Life', 'I-MISC'], [""'"", 'I-MISC'], ['s', 'I-MISC'], ['Too', 'I-MISC'], ['Short', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-11-22 16:32:13,On the plus side...“@newscientist: #Climate change has a silver lining: supersized sweet potatoes,en,120,14,1,[],neg,pos
2012-11-22 15:55:04,Gave a talk on energy and transport at Oxford Univ,en,72,11,1,"[['Oxford', 'I-ORG'], ['Univ', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-11-21 05:14:07,Exactly!,en,24,2,1,[],pos,neu
2012-11-21 03:01:08,Love this picture of the Curiousity rover on Mars. Landscape looks just like the California desert.,en,121,17,3,"[['Curiousity', 'I-MISC'], ['Mars', 'I-LOC'], ['California', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-11-20 19:32:50,"Btw, Elon Musk don't think Apple is doomed. Just won't unseat Google from 1st place with Larry P in charge.",en,121,20,3,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Apple', 'I-ORG'], ['Google', 'I-ORG'], ['Larry', 'I-PER'], ['P', 'I-PER']]",neg,neg
2012-11-20 19:22:29,"Mass. judge denies auto dealers' demand to kill our little Tesla store. Yay, justice prevails!",en,117,16,4,"[['Mass', 'I-LOC'], ['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2012-11-20 06:52:03,"Amos's article was fair, but Amos's's editor chose a more sensational headline used quotes even though Amos's didn't actually say quotes.",en,139,23,1,"[['Amos', 'I-PER'], ['Amos', 'I-ORG'], [""'"", 'I-ORG'], ['s', 'I-ORG'], ['Amos', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2012-11-20 06:38:31,These articles in Space News describe why Ariane 6 vs 5: and,en,104,14,1,"[['Space', 'I-ORG'], ['News', 'I-ORG'], ['Ariane', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-11-20 06:30:44,"Was misquoted by BBC as saying ""Europe's rocket has no chance"". Just said the [Franco-German] Ariane 5 has no chance, so go with Ariane 6.",en,138,25,2,"[['BBC', 'I-ORG'], ['Europe', 'I-LOC'], ['Franco', 'I-MISC'], ['-', 'I-MISC'], ['German', 'I-MISC'], ['Ariane', 'I-MISC'], ['5', 'I-MISC'], ['Ariane', 'I-MISC'], ['6', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neg
2012-11-19 06:59:46,"Just returned from a trip to London and Oxford, where Elon Musk met with many interesting people. Elon Musk really like Britain!",en,112,20,2,"[['London', 'I-LOC'], ['Oxford', 'I-LOC'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Britain', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-11-16 02:02:33,Original article on Model S from,en,72,8,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-11-16 01:25:08,Sounds like Consumer Reports had a good experience with the Tesla Model S,en,95,14,1,"[['Consumer', 'I-ORG'], ['Reports', 'I-ORG'], ['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-11-13 04:33:57,"Cool story about a installation after hurricane Sandy. Good going, guys!",en,105,13,3,"[['Sandy', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-11-12 08:39:13,Alexander Hamilton was awesome,en,52,5,1,"[['Alexander', 'I-PER'], ['Hamilton', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-11-07 21:46:38,View of Grasshopper test rocket from the water tower. Note SUV and person nearby for sense of size.,en,121,19,3,"[['Grasshopper', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-11-06 06:52:11,"Good skit by Henri, Le Chat Noir. Camus in cat form!",en,74,12,3,"[['Henri', 'I-PER'], ['Le', 'I-ORG'], ['Chat', 'I-ORG'], ['Noir', 'I-ORG'], ['Camus', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-11-03 20:51:36,"Engine gimbals for pitch and yaw, gas thrusters for roll.",en,66,11,1,[],pos,neu
2012-11-03 20:42:22,First flight of 10 story tall Grasshopper rocket using closed loop thrust vector throttle control,en,125,17,1,"[['Grasshopper', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-10-28 17:38:24,Reply to Our avg speed was ummm a little too high. Got a ticket at 92 mph on I-5. We need the Autobahn in CA!,en,120,26,3,"[['I', 'I-LOC'], ['5', 'I-MISC'], ['Autobahn', 'I-MISC'], ['CA', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neu
2012-10-28 17:25:15,V proud of Tesla team for completing 1000th Model S body. More cars made this month than entire rest of year,en,130,22,2,"[['V', 'I-ORG'], ['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-10-28 02:04:08,"Reply to Yes, Model S seats 5 adults + 2 kids with room for luggage in the front trunk. My kids love the rear facing seats best.",en,140,28,2,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-10-28 01:53:32,Pic of the Model S getting supercharged with the lovely,en,91,12,1,"[['Pic', 'I-PER'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-10-28 01:31:22,Doing LA to SF road trip in Model S with all 5 kids Talulah. Supercharger finished charging b4 we finished we's burgers!,en,125,23,2,"[['LA', 'I-LOC'], ['SF', 'I-LOC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Talulah', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2012-10-22 20:19:24,Just wrote a blog piece about Tesla stores,en,64,9,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neu
2012-10-11 22:59:26,Long exposure shot of Dragon and the Space Station arcing across the night sky over Texas,en,111,17,1,"[['Dragon', 'I-MISC'], ['Space', 'I-MISC'], ['Station', 'I-MISC'], ['Texas', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-10-08 00:50:33,Falcon 9 rocket booster has delivered Dragon to Dragon's target orbit!,en,65,11,1,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-10-07 20:45:44,Time lapse video of rocket roll out Now 3 hours 45 mins to lift off...,en,92,16,1,[],neg,neu
2012-10-04 02:31:38,An update about Tesla,en,44,5,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neu
2012-10-03 00:29:28,"Sorry, meant to say EDT.",en,34,6,1,[],neg,neg
2012-10-02 23:49:35,Launching our Falcon 9 rocket and Dragon spacecraft to the Space Station on Sunday at 8:35pm EST!,en,119,18,2,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC'], ['Space', 'I-LOC'], ['Station', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-10-01 20:39:28,Review of the Model S by,en,55,8,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-10-01 17:50:08,View from landing leg camera on Falcon rocket test rig (aka Grasshopper Project),en,103,14,1,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['Grasshopper', 'I-MISC'], ['Project', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neg
2012-09-30 22:01:54,"Now test firing our most advanced engine, the Merlin 1D-Vac, at 80 tons of thrust.",en,104,16,2,"[['Merlin', 'I-MISC'], ['1D', 'I-MISC'], ['-', 'I-MISC'], ['Vac', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2012-09-25 04:34:04,The Tesla Supercharger will over time allow you to travel anywhere on pure sunlight for free,en,114,17,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Supercharger', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-09-24 17:53:03,Model S review by Totally agree with criticisms. Corrections coming soon.,en,103,13,4,"[['S', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-09-22 00:36:50,First test flight hop of our Grasshopper VTVL rocket!,en,75,10,2,"[['Grasshopper', 'I-MISC'], ['VTVL', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2012-09-19 23:31:27,The first owner to drive coast to coast in a Model S is about to complete the journey,en,99,19,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-09-17 01:40:23,Tesla made 100 vehicle bodies this week for the first time. Really proud of the team! Pic of S/N 396:,en,123,21,3,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-09-14 01:27:09,Tesla Supercharger unveiling event set for Sept 24. It will feel like alien spaceships landed at highway rest stops.,en,116,19,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Supercharger', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-09-13 20:58:05,Amazing series of space pics assembled by,en,98,10,1,[],pos,pos
2012-09-06 20:00:47,Tesla Model S driven 285 miles from Vegas to the beach in LA on a single charge by,en,116,20,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Vegas', 'I-LOC'], ['LA', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-08-29 20:30:20,This piece about Mars in the NYT is worth a read,en,70,12,1,"[['Mars', 'I-LOC'], ['NYT', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-08-29 01:23:09,"Extending life to Mars would ensure humanity's survival and be the greatest, most exciting adventure ever!",en,120,17,1,"[['Mars', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-08-27 19:51:07,"Back of the envelope calc: Merlin wd accelerate Model S at 25 g's, so Merlin wd break sound barrier in &lt;1.5 sec",en,120,22,1,"[['Merlin', 'I-ORG'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Merlin', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2012-08-27 19:41:50,"For their test drive, their drove from LA to San Diego and back without recharging",en,119,19,1,"[['LA', 'I-LOC'], ['San', 'I-LOC'], ['Diego', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neu
2012-08-27 19:39:47,Motor Trend tests Model S as fastest American sedan at 3.9 sec 0-60 mph and tied for 1st worldwide in stopping distance,en,119,22,1,"[['Motor', 'I-ORG'], ['Trend', 'I-ORG'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['American', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2012-08-25 20:39:03,Neil Armstrong was a hero to all of humanity. Neil Armstrong's spirit will carry us to the stars.,en,84,17,2,"[['Neil', 'I-PER'], ['Armstrong', 'I-PER'], ['Neil', 'I-PER'], ['Armstrong', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-08-22 16:14:31,I love the sight of Teslas in the morning. Production line review is looking good!,en,104,16,3,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-08-22 16:11:24,Glad to contribute to the Tesla museum and will do more in the future. He was a great man.,en,112,20,3,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-08-13 21:47:27,About to go through my first jury selection process. Trial concerns an alleged gang related murder. Hardcore.,en,109,17,3,[],neg,neg
2012-08-04 00:23:11,"V important to make all of humanity proud, but in this case a particular duty is owed to the American taxpayer",en,120,22,1,"[['American', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-08-03 22:32:27,Deeply appreciate faith in We will do whatever it takes to make NASA and the American people proud.,en,116,20,2,"[['NASA', 'I-ORG'], ['American', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-08-03 17:38:43,Sure. To be clear that number would include all US solar energy (thermal+PV).,en,90,14,2,"[['US', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-08-03 02:11:15,1st pure solar gigawatt hour day just achieved by Predict 1st terawatt hour day from all US solar &lt; 15 years.,en,124,22,2,"[['US', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-08-01 03:37:27,I'm neither anti-conservative nor anti-liberal. Just don't like group think. Ideas should be considered on Ideas's own merits.,en,138,19,3,"[['Ideas', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2012-08-01 02:54:50,"Individuals set the vector for the tides. The Life of Brian points out that we are all individuals, except for that one guy.",en,133,24,2,"[['Life', 'I-MISC'], ['of', 'I-MISC'], ['Brian', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-08-01 02:32:59,People ought to think more about who wrote the software that's running in People's head (sigh). It probably wasn't them.,en,117,20,2,"[['People', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-08-01 02:30:53,"Don't know about ""dark manipulators"", but Adbusters played a major role in creating Occupy",en,121,16,1,"[['Adbusters', 'I-ORG'], ['Occupy', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-08-01 02:17:45,"Would love to make a Tesla supertruck with crazy torque, dynamic air suspension and corners like its on rails. make'd be sweet...",en,138,23,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-08-01 02:12:24,"Good assessment of the Dark Knight Rises in the Atlantic. Dickens, not Rand.",en,98,14,3,"[['Dark', 'I-MISC'], ['Knight', 'I-MISC'], ['Rises', 'I-MISC'], ['Atlantic', 'I-LOC'], ['Dickens', 'I-PER'], ['Rand', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-07-31 22:05:26,Model S starts at $50k after federal rebate. Gen3 will be ~$30k. Need to optimize design and scale volume.,en,122,20,3,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S3', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-07-31 21:57:37,Goal for Model S is to show that electric is way way better than gas. Combine w solar power the future looks bright.,en,122,24,2,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-07-31 03:19:34,Worth noting that Muller's research confirming global warming is real was funded by Koch. Fate loves irony.,en,107,17,2,"[['Muller', 'I-PER'], ['Koch', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-07-27 20:40:28,Olympics opening is excellently British. Jolly good show!,en,79,9,3,"[['Olympics', 'I-MISC'], ['British', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-07-27 17:47:44,Abandoned car and biked across London. Super fun! Next time minus the tweed jacket.,en,105,15,4,"[['London', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-07-27 03:38:47,"Yes, my absolute goal w Tesla has always been mass market electric cars. Will finally get there with Gen3 program.",en,122,21,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['Gen3', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-07-27 03:33:35,Now it's just a song that you used to know,en,64,11,1,[],neg,neu
2012-07-27 03:15:29,"Biggest risk is that we take too long to solve the sustainable energy problem, causing climate change meltdown.",en,118,19,1,[],neg,neg
2012-07-27 02:26:31,"Compared to past, today's world is fantastic likely will be for many decades. Just need to cover future downside risk.",en,124,21,2,[],pos,pos
2012-07-27 01:13:28,Asimov's Foundation points out that all civilizations fall. Must ensure dark period is short finite.,en,124,17,2,"[['Asimov', 'I-ORG'], [""'"", 'I-ORG'], ['s', 'I-ORG'], ['Foundation', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-07-23 06:48:09,Big oil is pulling same trick about smoking the atmosphere ... diff is we only have 1 atmosphere:,en,119,19,1,[],neg,neg
2012-07-23 06:39:10,"30 years ago, when 98% of scientists said smoking caused cancer, tobacco industry response was still ""scientists disagree""",en,122,18,1,[],neg,neg
2012-07-21 17:09:04,"Now debating the nature of citizen and state, effective democracy necessary revolution, moderated by",en,122,16,1,[],pos,pos
2012-07-21 16:27:01,"Heard an interesting comment at the debate: ""If we see no angels in others, we harbor none in we.""",en,105,19,1,[],neg,pos
2012-07-21 15:40:07,Am in Yellowstone at an Oxford style debate about women and society. I'm in favor :),en,84,16,2,"[['Yellowstone', 'I-LOC'], ['Oxford', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-07-17 11:16:22,"""Welcome qwerty monkey Jesus love"" are the top 5 most popular passwords after ""password"".",en,112,15,2,"[['Jesus', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-07-15 07:34:14,Will publish something on the Hyperloop in about four weeks. Will forgo patents on the idea and just open source the idea. Not a vac tunnel btw.,en,138,26,3,"[['Hyperloop', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neu
2012-07-15 07:30:06,"""Most of us live in a semi-somnambulistic state the days fly by. The 2 exceptions are childhood and when we are in love."" - RG",en,132,26,3,"[['R', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-07-14 05:01:46,"Headed to a (ahem) volcano caldera. Since Elon Musk didn't finish my PhD, it's actually ""Mr."" Evil.",en,113,17,3,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Mr', 'I-PER'], ['""', 'I-PER'], ['Evil', 'I-PER']]",neg,neg
2012-07-12 14:57:32,I think we will see people on Mars in less than 20 years. 12 to 15 years most likely. #OccupyMars,en,104,21,3,"[['MarsccM', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-07-12 14:50:49,"Going at full speed! MT “@iansomerhalder: Elon- Elon- are @iansomerhalder's hero @iansomerhalder's friend.Please!Ramp up production on cars that use NO gas.""",en,125,21,2,"[['ansomer', 'I-ORG'], ['Elon', 'I-ORG'], ['Elonansomeransomer', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-07-07 07:17:10,Now back to work. Intense months ahead as we ramp production of rockets and cars.,en,81,15,2,[],pos,pos
2012-07-05 10:19:25,"Moonbow's are real, btw. I'm not on acid :) Here is what we saw:",en,86,15,2,"[['Moonbow', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2012-07-05 07:41:16,Am standing on the beach in Maui and looking at a moon rainbow for the first time in my life. Incredibly beautiful.,en,115,22,2,"[['Maui', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-07-01 03:27:27,"After 2008 meltdown, vacation for Elon Musk just meant email with a view, but SpaceX Tesla are now strong enough that Elon Musk can make vacation for Elon Musk real (yay!!)",en,143,27,1,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['SpaceX', 'I-ORG'], ['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-07-01 03:08:36,Screening of Baseball in the Time of Cholera (dir: prod me) at WME July 12. hosting,en,139,21,2,"[['Baseball', 'I-MISC'], ['in', 'I-MISC'], ['Time', 'I-MISC'], ['of', 'I-MISC'], ['Choa', 'I-MISC'], ['WME', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2012-06-30 02:45:18,"Thanks Dan, Dan are a good sportsman. Elon Musk will still donate to DWB as though Elon Musk'd lost.",en,106,18,3,"[['Dan', 'I-PER'], ['Dan', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['DWB', 'I-ORG'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-06-28 14:59:35,"""The Girl Who Fixed the Umlaut""",en,65,8,1,"[['The', 'I-MISC'], ['Girl', 'I-MISC'], ['Who', 'I-MISC'], ['Fi', 'I-MISC'], ['Umlaut', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-06-27 14:43:04,"She was a great woman “@VanityFair: In Memoriam, Nora Ephron, 1941-2012",en,94,12,1,"[['VanityFair', 'I-ORG'], ['Nora', 'I-PER'], ['Ephron', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-06-27 13:33:51,Meant to post this link for Merlin:,en,57,8,1,"[['Merlin', 'I-PER']]",pos,neu
2012-06-27 13:31:37,"Merlin fired at full thrust! Engine weighs half a ton, but has power equal to several Hoover Dams",en,119,19,2,"[['Merlin', 'I-ORG'], ['Hoover', 'I-MISC'], ['Dam', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2012-06-22 22:18:45,Model S review by Motor Trend,en,51,7,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Motor', 'I-ORG'], ['Trend', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2012-06-22 22:16:33,About to deliver the first ten Model S cars from,en,62,11,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-06-20 16:16:50,Dragon will use four pairs of side mounted Superdraco engines. Can function with up to four out.,en,113,18,2,"[['Dragon', 'I-ORG'], ['Superdraco', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2012-06-18 21:27:46,Just fired our Superdraco escape rocket engine at full thrust! Needed to carry astronauts on Dragon,en,121,17,2,"[['Superdraco', 'I-ORG'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2012-06-18 08:31:06,Wore Marquis de Sade outfit for a party last night. Was v popular with women who'd read 50 Shades :),en,122,21,2,"[['Marquis', 'I-PER'], ['de', 'I-PER'], ['Sade', 'I-PER'], ['50', 'I-MISC'], ['Shades', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-06-14 07:54:02,"While in Austin, had a great time doing a cameo in latest movie, Machete Kills. Cool studio on old airport.",en,118,21,2,"[['Austin', 'I-LOC'], ['Machete', 'I-MISC'], ['Kills', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-06-14 07:26:23,"Charlie Bolden, NASA Administrator, checks out Dragon at NASA's central Texas test site",en,106,14,1,"[['Charlie', 'I-PER'], ['Bolden', 'I-PER'], ['NASA', 'I-ORG'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC'], ['NASA', 'I-ORG'], ['Texas', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-06-05 17:16:33,Spacecraft arrives at Port of Los Angeles for transfer to SpaceX test facilities in Texas,en,111,16,1,"[['Port', 'I-LOC'], ['of', 'I-LOC'], ['Los', 'I-LOC'], ['Angeles', 'I-LOC'], ['SpaceX', 'I-ORG'], ['Texas', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-05-31 21:09:28,Dragon floating in the Pacific near California. Reentry scorch marks visible on the heat shield,en,117,16,2,"[['Dragon', 'I-MISC'], ['Pacific', 'I-LOC'], ['California', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neu
2012-05-31 15:48:16,Splashdown successful!! Sending fast boat to Dragon lat/long provided by P3 tracking planes #Dragon,en,99,14,2,"[['Dragon', 'I-LOC'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-05-31 14:31:25,Thrusters will also fire during reentry to adjust touchdown point. Next version will land w helicopter precision #Dragon,en,120,18,2,"[['Dragon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2012-05-31 14:21:33,Spaceship has departed from the International Space Station. Firing thrusters to deorbit in ~30 mins #Dragon,en,108,16,2,"[['International', 'I-LOC'], ['Space', 'I-LOC'], ['Station', 'I-LOC'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neg
2012-05-25 20:23:00,Space Station tracking spaceship docking approach vector #Dragon,en,87,9,1,[],pos,neu
2012-05-25 15:41:31,Dragon captured by the International Space Station! Just awesome ...,en,90,11,2,"[['International', 'I-LOC'], ['Space', 'I-LOC'], ['Station', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-05-24 18:15:19,Dragon flies over the SpaceX #GrasshopperProject at our central Texas test site. It will jump soon.,en,121,17,3,"[['Dragon', 'I-ORG'], ['SpaceX', 'I-MISC'], ['#', 'I-MISC'], ['GrasshopperProject', 'I-MISC'], ['Texas', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-05-24 17:34:28,The head of the Russian Space Agency and some Russian diplomats are visiting today. Looking forward to meeting.,en,119,19,2,"[['Russian', 'I-ORG'], ['Space', 'I-ORG'], ['Agency', 'I-ORG'], ['Russian', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-05-24 06:23:53,About 110 miles away and the spacecraft is now in direct communication with the Space Station #Dragon,en,101,17,1,"[['Space', 'I-MISC'], ['Station', 'I-MISC'], ['#', 'I-MISC'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-05-24 03:35:55,"The President just called to say congrats. Caller ID was blocked, so at first Elon Musk thought Caller ID was a telemarketer :)",en,112,21,2,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['ID', 'I-PER']]",neg,pos
2012-05-23 15:09:40,Dragon fly by of Space Station planned for 12:47 am California time. All systems green. #dragonlaunch,en,101,16,3,"[['Space', 'I-LOC'], ['Station', 'I-LOC'], ['California', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-05-22 12:27:20,Launch video of Falcon 9 from Cape Canaveral tracking cameras #dragonlaunch,en,97,12,1,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC'], ['Cape', 'I-LOC'], ['Canaveral', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-05-22 10:38:25,Navigation bay pointing to deep space and star map being generated by star tracker one. Yes! #DragonLaunch,en,106,17,3,"[['Dragon', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-05-22 10:31:20,Dragon spaceship opens the navigation pod bay door without hesitation. So much nicer than HAL9000 :) #DragonLaunch,en,114,17,2,"[['DragonAL9000', 'I-MISC'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-05-22 08:56:05,"Also big thanks to the Air Force, FAA and all of our partners for the Air Force, FAA and all of our partners's support of this mission.",en,96,19,1,"[['Air', 'I-ORG'], ['Force', 'I-ORG'], ['FAA', 'I-ORG'], ['Air', 'I-ORG'], ['Force', 'I-ORG'], ['FAA', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-05-22 08:52:56,"Huge appreciation for without whom we could not even have started, let alone reached this far.",en,101,17,1,[],pos,pos
2012-05-22 08:04:05,"Falcon flew perfectly!! Dragon in orbit, comm locked and solar arrays active!! Feels like a giant weight just came off my back :)",en,129,23,3,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-05-22 07:43:41,T minus 60 seconds. Terminal autosequence initiated. #DragonLaunch,en,66,8,3,"[['DragonLnch', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neu
2012-05-22 07:34:32,T minus 10 minutes ... Entering terminal count #dragonlaunch,en,60,9,2,[],neg,neu
2012-05-22 03:05:10,Major Tesla milestone: All crash testing is complete for 5* (max) safety rating. Cars can now be built for sale to public!,en,122,22,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-05-20 23:44:11,Just did an interview with Spaceflight Now. Some of your questions may be answered here:,en,110,16,2,"[['Spaceflight', 'I-ORG'], ['Now', 'I-ORG']]",neg,neu
2012-05-20 23:13:34,"Simulations show launch ok with bad valve. Still, better to stop fix. Recalling rockets after launch is not an option.",en,124,21,3,[],neg,neg
2012-05-19 09:06:31,Launch aborted: slightly high combustion chamber pressure on engine 5. Will adjust limits for countdown in a few days.,en,118,19,2,[],neg,neg
2012-05-19 08:15:48,"Whatever happens today, we could not have done it without but errors are we's alone and Elon Musk most of all.",en,110,21,1,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-05-14 02:07:17,Must remember not to refer to Chimpanzees as deadly killing machines when taking little kids to see a movie about Chimpanzees,en,118,21,1,"[['Chimpanzee', 'I-MISC'], ['Chimpanzee', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2012-05-11 00:58:31,... which is the critical breakthrough needed for life to become multiplanetary.,en,80,12,1,[],pos,neg
2012-05-11 00:55:26,Making large scale rocket propulsion landing work well is a critical step towards a fully reusable Mars transport system,en,120,19,1,"[['Mars', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2012-05-11 00:47:27,Landing gear of the mega thrust propulsive landing rocket done (next gen Falcon). First hops soon.,en,121,17,3,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-05-10 16:24:47,"Meant to say: prizes for first 10 who do 400 miles in Tesla w/o recharging, not nonstop, which would require diapers :)",en,119,22,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-05-09 23:54:36,Model S exceeds 300 mile range target! Prize for the 1st person to do LA-SF nonstop (400 miles),en,117,19,2,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['LA', 'I-MISC'], ['SF', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-05-08 05:45:09,Saw The Dictator yesterday. Reminded Elon Musk of The Dictator's reelection. Seems like only yesterday since The Dictator was last in power.,en,116,19,3,"[['The', 'I-PER'], ['Dictator', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['The', 'I-PER'], ['Diator', 'I-PER'], ['The', 'I-PER'], ['Dictator', 'I-PER']]",neg,pos
2012-05-05 01:05:36,Dragon code is written in C++ on Linux.,en,48,9,1,"[['Dragon', 'I-ORG'], ['C', 'I-MISC'], ['+', 'I-MISC'], ['+', 'I-MISC'], ['Linux', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-05-05 00:59:37,"Almost done reviewing Dragon code with Looks good so far. Target launch date is May 19, right after Soyuz docks.",en,119,21,3,"[['Dragon', 'I-ORG'], ['Soyuz', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-05-03 18:27:19,"For humanity to have an exciting inspiring future, we cannot be confined to Earth forever. #APSpaceChat",en,124,18,2,"[['EarthC', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-05-03 18:22:41,Definitely. Long term goal of SpaceX making life multiplanetary. #OccupyMars #APSpaceChat,en,101,12,3,"[['SpaceXcc', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-05-03 18:15:01,"Ignition by John Clarke, Huzel Wang book on propulsion, Asimov's Foundation, Heinlein's MiaHM #APSpaceChat",en,121,16,1,"[['John', 'I-PER'], ['Clarke', 'I-PER'], ['Huzel', 'I-PER'], ['Wang', 'I-PER'], ['Asimov', 'I-MISC'], ['Foundation', 'I-ORG'], ['Heinlein', 'I-PER'], ['Mia', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-04-30 20:22:34,"Woohoo, rocket hold down firing completed and all looks good!!",en,62,10,2,[],pos,pos
2012-04-30 20:10:22,T minus five minutes to flame,en,29,6,1,[],neg,neu
2012-04-30 19:45:25,Flight computer aborted rocket hold down firing. Anomaly addressed. Cycling systems to countdown,en,118,14,3,[],neg,neg
2012-04-30 15:30:50,Am excited to announce that SolarCity has filed for an IPO. Mission is to bring affordable solar power to the people!,en,117,21,2,"[['SolarCity', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-04-24 20:17:02,Just confirmed with that May 7th is go for launch of Falcon 9 Dragon to the Space Station,en,101,20,1,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC'], ['Space', 'I-LOC'], ['Station', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-04-23 20:55:21,Am pushing launch back approx a week to do more testing on Dragon docking code. New date pending coordination with,en,121,21,2,"[['Dragon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-04-23 04:02:38,Just completed the rocket rollout review at SpaceX HQ in California. Almost time to launch. Pucker factor increasing...,en,119,18,3,"[['SpaceX', 'I-ORG'], ['California', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-04-22 00:14:01,In NYC for the premiere of Baseball in the Time of Great work by and,en,102,18,2,"[['NYC', 'I-LOC'], ['Baseball', 'I-MISC'], ['in', 'I-MISC'], ['the', 'I-MISC'], ['Time', 'I-MISC'], ['of', 'I-MISC'], ['Great', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-04-21 08:28:51,I feel compelled to state the obvious fact that Coachella is excellent.,en,93,13,2,"[['Coachella', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-04-19 20:47:21,Basic premise is that it's better to try to address some of the world's problems than to create an aristocracy of wealth,en,120,22,1,[],neg,pos
2012-04-19 20:39:12,Just signed Giving Pledge with 11 others. Elon Musk hope this announcement convinces others to do the same.,en,121,18,3,"[['P', 'I-MISC'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",neg,pos
2012-04-18 19:48:14,"When holding my new white cat, Elon Musk feel a strange desire for Bob's Big Boy and sharks with lasers",en,117,20,1,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Bob', 'I-PER'], ['s', 'I-MISC'], ['Big', 'I-MISC'], ['Boy', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-04-14 22:52:27,Great work by APJ “@brynmooser: The foundation is nearly complete at the school,en,120,15,1,"[['APJ', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-04-11 00:20:22,Great to meet Jon Stewart this eve. Have been a fan of for a billion years.,en,89,17,2,"[['Jon', 'I-PER'], ['Stewart', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-04-09 19:50:03,Friend told Elon Musk about the amazing work of Brazilian plastic surgeon Evil Picante. He was actually saying Ivo Pitanguy.,en,117,19,2,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Brazilian', 'I-MISC'], ['Evil', 'I-PER'], ['Picante', 'I-PER'], ['Ivo', 'I-PER'], ['Pitanguy', 'I-PER']]",neg,pos
2012-04-09 02:04:53,"Besides ensuring the continuance of life, creating a base on Mars would be the most exciting adventure ever!",en,108,18,1,"[['Mars', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-04-09 02:01:15,Interview in Nature describing why we should extend life to Mars,en,86,12,1,"[['Nature', 'I-ORG'], ['Mars', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-04-05 23:35:14,"Wow, a Tesla owner in Europe just passed 200,000 km while racing a Tesla owner in Europe's Roadster!",en,100,15,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Europe', 'I-LOC'], ['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Europe', 'I-LOC'], ['Roadster', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-04-05 17:21:45,"Judge dismisses lawsuit to take the happy out of ""Happy Meal""",en,83,12,1,"[['Happy', 'I-MISC'], ['Meal', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-04-04 01:58:25,Huge tornadoes in Texas tossing truck trailers through the air. Hope people are ok.,en,105,15,2,"[['Texas', 'I-LOC']]",neg,pos
2012-04-03 09:16:42,Also dig Mass Effect. It's all fun & games until the AI decides people suck. Maybe we can be the AI's limbic system.,en,113,22,3,"[['Mass', 'I-MISC'], ['Effect', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-04-03 08:45:18,Bioshock is an Ayn Rand dystopia and Fallout New Vegas is a Hegelian dialectic. Games have come a long way since Pong.,en,118,22,2,"[['Bioshock', 'I-MISC'], ['Ayn', 'I-MISC'], ['Rand', 'I-MISC'], ['Fallout', 'I-MISC'], ['New', 'I-MISC'], ['Vegas', 'I-MISC'], ['Hegelian', 'I-MISC'], ['Pong', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-04-01 18:44:24,"UN must take responsibility & help people of Haiti. MT ""@brynmooser: Front page NYTimes.",en,114,15,3,"[['UN', 'I-ORG'], ['Haiti', 'I-LOC'], ['M', 'I-LOC'], ['NYTimes', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-03-31 17:43:06,Having dinner where a dude is hanging giant underwear with a cherry picker.,en,98,14,2,[],pos,neu
2012-03-31 16:42:30,Happy bday to my old and dear friend U do parties better than a rockstar. For Berlin ...,en,122,20,3,"[['Berlin', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-03-28 00:32:07,"The Model S beta endurance car just passed 150,000 miles on a single battery pack!",en,82,15,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-03-22 07:10:10,Interesting interview with Vinge about superhuman AI and optimistic apocalypses,en,101,11,1,"[['Vinge', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-03-20 21:05:26,Support as they try to save a good satellite from becoming space junk. Let it live! #antarctica,en,134,19,3,[],pos,pos
2012-03-15 09:37:28,Lovely poster about wishes that explains one of the many reasons to make life multiplanetary,en,114,16,1,[],pos,pos
2012-03-15 01:36:58,"10 years ago today, SpaceX was founded. Many battles fought. Physics always won.",en,102,14,4,"[['SpaceX', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neg
2012-03-14 23:06:03,"Why I'm leaving the Empire, by Darth Vader",en,65,9,1,"[['Empire', 'I-ORG'], ['Darth', 'I-PER'], ['Vader', 'I-PER']]",pos,neu
2012-03-13 07:27:14,"If something is physically possible, not only is someone doing something, but there is also an award show.",en,99,18,1,[],pos,pos
2012-03-12 06:45:14,"Mountain lions eat cats, which means we *actually* live in a cat eat cat world ... an apology is owed to dogkind!",en,113,22,1,[],neg,pos
2012-03-11 16:21:59,"I think if you go there, they just feed you delicious candy all day and ask nothing in return.",en,94,19,1,[],pos,pos
2012-03-11 15:31:43,Just passed a place called the Sugar Shack in a Louisiana swamp. Elon Musk wonder what happens there?,en,115,18,3,"[['Sugar', 'I-LOC'], ['Shack', 'I-LOC'], ['Louisiana', 'I-LOC'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,neu
2012-03-07 01:52:14,The President of Serbia came by our booth at the Geneva Motor Show and talked about Nikola Tesla,en,118,19,1,"[['Serbia', 'I-LOC'], ['Geneva', 'I-MISC'], ['Motor', 'I-MISC'], ['Show', 'I-MISC'], ['Nikola', 'I-PER'], ['Tesla', 'I-PER']]",pos,neu
2012-03-02 00:29:56,Dawn at Cape Canaveral,en,44,5,1,"[['Cape', 'I-LOC'], ['Canaveral', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-02-29 07:02:03,"Studied physics in college, read a lot of books and was taught by the world's leading domain experts at SpaceX.",en,120,21,1,"[['SpaceX', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2012-02-28 22:25:50,"Falcon 9 and Dragon now vertical on the launch pad, surrounded by 300 ft tall lightning towers",en,116,18,1,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-02-25 22:17:04,"Yes, this will, if all goes well, be the first commercial spaceship to dock with the Space Station. T zero ~ end of April.",en,133,25,2,"[['Space', 'I-LOC'], ['Station', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-02-25 22:04:41,Dragon spaceship and Falcon 9 rocket just completed final assembly at Cape Canaveral,en,106,14,1,"[['Dragon', 'I-MISC'], ['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC'], ['Cape', 'I-LOC'], ['Canaveral', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-02-25 18:36:12,Supporting the drive to get a #PlutoStamp for the New Horizons mission,en,76,13,1,"[['Pluto', 'I-MISC'], ['New', 'I-MISC'], ['Horizons', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-02-22 00:57:28,launched a rocket into the northern lights,en,70,9,1,[],pos,pos
2012-02-21 16:27:16,"Iran's nuclear weapons facility is apparently called ""Frodo"". Watch out for Gollum! Gollum's precious...",en,120,15,3,"[['Iran', 'I-LOC'], ['Frodo', 'I-LOC'], ['Gollum', 'I-PER'], ['Gollum', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-02-17 00:51:21,Important point highlighted by an electric car in California produces only 1/4 CO2 of gasoline,en,123,17,1,"[['California', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-02-14 01:32:06,Model X review by Jim Motavalli. Elon Musk think Elon Musk likes Model X.,en,80,13,3,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['X', 'I-MISC'], ['Jim', 'I-PER'], ['Motavalli', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['X', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-02-12 20:37:52,"At the Samovar having tea called ""monkey picked iron goddess of mercy"". Those monkeys sure know Those monkeys's tea.",en,128,19,3,"[['Samovar', 'I-LOC']]",neg,pos
2012-02-10 19:54:59,Do not search for purple squirrels! Giving purple squirrels attention only makes purple squirrels want to be more purple.,en,97,17,2,[],neg,pos
2012-02-10 19:38:00,"Tesla Model X is 3rd most searched term on Google, right after purple squirrel. Damn you squirrel!",en,120,18,3,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['X', 'I-MISC'], ['Google', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neg
2012-02-10 17:23:17,Tesla Model X video,it,42,5,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['X', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-02-10 16:51:47,"Don't worry, we've got a cool solution for ski storage on the X with the Falcon wing doors",en,104,19,1,"[['X', 'I-MISC'], ['Falcon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-02-09 20:00:42,"Btw, Foster the People is playing the Model X event tonight. Seemed like the right vibe.",en,88,16,2,"[['Foster', 'I-ORG'], ['the', 'I-ORG'], ['People', 'I-ORG'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['X', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-02-09 16:37:45,Model X sketch showing just a bit more leg. Unveiling tonight...,en,86,12,2,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['X', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neu
2012-02-08 19:13:44,"Cool new pic of the most powerful type of solar flare, called X-class. Am not making this up!",en,121,20,3,"[['X', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-02-08 04:40:20,Russia and China are blocking UN action. Can't imagine why Russia and China wouldn't support a democratic uprising...,en,105,16,2,"[['Russia', 'I-LOC'], ['China', 'I-LOC'], ['UN', 'I-ORG'], ['Russia', 'I-LOC'], ['China', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neg
2012-02-08 04:35:43,Wish there was something we could do to help the people of Syria.,en,89,14,2,"[['Syria', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-02-07 07:13:16,"Yes, we will unveil a fully functional advanced prototype of the Model X -- almost identical to production.",en,120,19,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['X', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-02-06 01:44:18,The sheer size of Falcon Heavy is mind-blowing. Falcon Heavy could literally send a fully loaded London bus to the moon.,en,110,20,2,"[['Falcon', 'I-ORG'], ['Heavy', 'I-ORG'], ['Falcon', 'I-ORG'], ['Heavy', 'I-ORG'], ['London', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2012-02-06 01:33:43,The London Sunday Times created a chart showing how Falcon compares to the Saturn V and Shuttle,en,117,18,1,"[['The', 'I-ORG'], ['London', 'I-ORG'], ['Sunday', 'I-ORG'], ['Times', 'I-ORG'], ['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['Saturn', 'I-MISC'], ['V', 'I-MISC'], ['Shuttle', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-02-05 20:07:16,Just posted a photo,en,41,5,1,[],neg,neu
2012-02-04 20:42:54,"Yeah, we will stream the whole mission realtime with no buffer. You see what we see.",en,96,17,2,[],pos,neu
2012-02-04 02:28:24,Docking with Space Station now likely to happen in April. Hopefully will look something like this:,en,120,17,2,"[['Space', 'I-ORG'], ['Station', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-02-02 17:00:34,The most interesting view of the Model X is really with the doors open,en,92,15,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['X', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-02-01 16:03:05,Just test-fired the Superdraco rocket engine. Enables launch escape and landing on thrusters. SpaceX.com,en,126,15,3,"[['Superdraco', 'I-MISC'], ['SpaceX', 'I-ORG'], ['.', 'I-ORG'], ['com', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-02-01 09:12:24,"Um, while awesome in its own way, its was not actually the SpaceX theme song. It seems that irony is sometimes lost in a tweet.",en,128,25,2,"[['SpaceX', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2012-01-31 16:49:58,The SpaceX theme song by Total Ghost is just too good ... ooh ooh ooh,en,91,16,1,"[['SpaceX', 'I-ORG'], ['Total', 'I-PER'], ['Ghost', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-01-28 19:54:40,The lady doth protest too little.,en,55,7,2,[],neg,neg
2012-01-28 02:21:03,The Model X unveiling will be webcast live on at 8pm on Feb 9th. Most cars are pretty blah. This is not.,en,126,23,3,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['X', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-01-27 20:35:04,Beautiful picture of Earth from the new NASA satellite,en,76,10,1,"[['Earth', 'I-LOC'], ['NASA', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2012-01-24 04:16:39,Rough cut simulation of the SpaceX next gen rocket & spaceship design,en,91,13,1,"[['SpaceX', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neg
2012-01-24 04:03:10,Design completed for bringing rocket back to launchpad using only thrusters. Yay. Wings r just dead weight in space.,en,116,19,3,[],pos,neg
2012-01-24 03:04:49,Strongest solar radiation storm in 7 years is blasting Earth. This huge eruption hits us tomorrow:,en,120,17,2,"[['Earth', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-01-23 01:42:54,Bought some wood and built a little treehouse with my boys. Few more beautiful ways to spend an afternoon.,en,106,19,2,[],pos,pos
2012-01-22 00:44:23,I heard Lars von Trier optioned the movie rights,en,58,10,1,"[['Lars', 'I-PER'], ['von', 'I-PER'], ['Trier', 'I-PER']]",neg,neu
2012-01-18 01:54:53,"That said, even though they cause Elon Musk grief, Elon Musk would defend the right of shorts to exist. shorts are often unreasonably maligned.",en,126,22,2,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",neg,neg
2012-01-17 22:07:50,That's not just paranoia (a healthy trait at times). Tesla really is under massive attack by short sellers,en,128,19,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2012-01-17 17:47:19,Will communicate better in the future. Too many people want us to fail and are willing to twist any bit of news against us.,en,126,24,2,[],neg,neg
2012-01-17 17:44:57,"TSLA down ~$500M Friday, but back up ~$500M today. Sorry for the roller coaster.",en,80,14,2,"[['TSLA', 'I-ORG']]",neg,neg
2012-01-14 20:29:34,"Somebody needs to tell Kim Jong-un that the showbiz phrase ""break a leg"" doesn't mean what Kim Jong-un thinks the showbiz phrase ""break a leg"" does",en,108,20,1,"[['Kim', 'I-PER'], ['Jong', 'I-PER'], ['un', 'I-PER'], ['Kim', 'I-PER'], ['Jong', 'I-PER'], ['un', 'I-PER']]",neg,neu
2012-01-14 20:27:41,"Once more, with feeling! ""North Korea Punishes Insincere Mourners""",en,89,10,2,"[['North', 'I-LOC'], ['Korea', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neg
2012-01-13 05:49:17,"A Tesla Roadster just passed the 100,000 mile mark for the first time and still has over 200 miles of range.",en,108,21,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Roadster', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-01-12 23:07:42,What is more magical than cowboys herding cats? Livin' the dream...,en,90,12,2,[],pos,pos
2012-01-12 21:07:59,"Kids these days are so grown up! RT ""Second-Graders Wow Audience With School Production Of Equus""",en,119,17,2,"[['R', 'I-ORG'], ['Eus', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-01-12 02:47:48,Model S Performance powertrain produced so much torque today that we broke the dyno. 4.4 sec 0-60 mph will not be a problem.,en,124,23,2,"[['Model', 'I-ORG'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Performance', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neg
2012-01-11 02:36:39,"The exec conf room at Tesla used to be called Denali, but Elon Musk decided to move a few letters around. Seemed more apt :)",en,138,25,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['Denali', 'I-ORG'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",neg,pos
2012-01-06 20:09:40,Model S Signature series sold out as of today,en,68,10,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Sign', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2012-01-06 17:30:01,Next month is also when our Dragon spaceship docks with the Space Station for the first time. Major pucker factor...,en,116,20,2,"[['Dragon', 'I-ORG'], ['Space', 'I-LOC'], ['Station', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neu
2012-01-06 17:28:01,Feb is huge month. Model X world premier and public reveal of our LA design studio on the 9th. Stay tuned for more details.,en,123,24,3,"[['Model', 'I-ORG'], ['X', 'I-ORG'], ['LA', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2012-01-03 21:28:25,Just finished Massie's book on Catherine. Massie's book on Catherine CatherineHighly recommend.,en,130,18,3,"[['Massie', 'I-PER'], ['Catherine', 'I-PER'], ['Massie', 'I-PER'], ['Catherine', 'I-PER'], ['Catherine', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-01-03 21:04:51,"Respectfully disagree. Larry made awesome moves last year, which laid the foundation for G+ to kick butt in 2012. Larry's a stud.",en,131,23,3,"[['Larry', 'I-PER'], ['Larry', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2012-01-03 06:58:13,"What everyone really thinks ... RT “@jonlovett: If Mayans were good at predicting the future, there'd be Mayans.”",en,113,18,1,"[['R', 'I-ORG'], ['Mayans', 'I-MISC'], ['Mayans', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2012-01-01 21:52:44,"On a lighter note, the RHCP are f* awesome. No better way to bring in the New Year...",en,107,19,2,"[['R', 'I-ORG'], ['New', 'I-MISC'], ['Year', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-01-01 20:49:05,I said *information* weapons for a reason. The bit is mightier than the bomb.,en,77,14,2,[],neg,pos
2012-01-01 20:41:34,"If we are not careful, we will find that knife against liberty's neck. Fate has a great sense of irony.",en,125,21,3,[],pos,pos
2012-01-01 20:33:16,"We built powerful information weapons to fight enemies of liberty. Now enemies of liberty are largely defeated, but powerful information weapons remain.",en,130,20,2,[],pos,neg
2012-01-01 16:54:27,"However, China's real estate crisis will explode in a way that makes ours look puny. They can't hide China's real estate crisis for much longer.",en,135,23,2,"[['China', 'I-LOC'], ['China', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neg
2012-01-01 16:49:40,"Yeah, 2012 will be great for the American economy & jobs, as we've mostly dealt with the overbuilt housing crisis.",en,129,21,1,"[['American', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2012-01-01 16:40:27,"My first prediction of 2012 has come true: ouch, My's head hurts.",en,63,12,1,"[['My', 'I-PER']]",neg,neg
2011-12-31 22:08:42,World violence being super low is probably counter-intuitive to most people. is's because modern media is a misery microscope.,en,128,19,2,[],neg,neg
2011-12-31 22:05:47,Here's a happy thought for 2012: world violence is at an all time historical low. Excellent piece by Stephen Pinker,en,137,21,2,"[['Stephen', 'I-PER'], ['Pinker', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2011-12-31 13:06:23,Hacked my Tesla charge connector on a small island in the rain last night #whatcouldpossiblygowrong,en,99,15,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neg
2011-12-30 15:35:47,"Not that this really matters. All current rocket tech, including ours, sucks. Only when All current rocket tech, including ours becomes fully reusable, will All current rocket tech, including ours not suck.",en,132,22,3,[],neg,pos
2011-12-30 14:48:52,"SpaceX has Boeing, Lockheed, Europe (Ariane) and Russia (Proton/Soyuz) near checkmate in rocket technology. End game is all about China.",en,136,20,2,"[['SpaceX', 'I-ORG'], ['Boeing', 'I-ORG'], ['Lockheed', 'I-ORG'], ['Europe', 'I-LOC'], ['Ariane', 'I-ORG'], ['Russia', 'I-LOC'], ['Proton', 'I-ORG'], ['/', 'I-ORG'], ['Soyuz', 'I-ORG'], ['China', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neu
2011-12-30 14:36:17,China unveils ambitious space strategy,en,60,6,1,"[['China', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2011-12-30 04:57:23,"To be clear, CtG absolutely did *not* bang CtG's horse. They were just close friends who liked to take showers together and spoon at night.",en,137,25,2,"[['CtG', 'I-ORG'], ['CG', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2011-12-30 04:10:31,"Right mood, scented candles, Barry White singing ""Can't Get Enough of Your Love, Baby"" and the magic (by that Elon Musk mean horsef*ing) happens ...",en,140,24,1,"[['Barry', 'I-PER'], ['White', 'I-PER'], ['Can', 'I-MISC'], ['t', 'I-MISC'], ['Get', 'I-MISC'], ['Enough', 'I-MISC'], ['of', 'I-MISC'], ['Your', 'I-MISC'], ['Love', 'I-MISC'], [',', 'I-MISC'], ['Baby', 'I-MISC'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2011-12-30 04:03:42,I'm just saying that u shouldn't pass judgment based on one night of passion. Sometimes things just happen and u go with the moment :),en,134,25,2,[],pos,pos
2011-12-30 03:58:30,"Sew one button, doesn't make u a tailor; cook one meal, doesn't make u a chef; but f* one horse and u r a horsef*er for all of history...",en,137,29,1,[],neg,neu
2011-12-30 03:53:51,"Am reading Robert Massie's book on Catherine the Great. Yeah, Elon Musk know what you're probably thinking ... did Catherine the Great really f* a horse?",en,129,23,2,"[['Robert', 'I-PER'], ['Massie', 'I-PER'], ['Catherine', 'I-PER'], ['the', 'I-PER'], ['Great', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Catherine', 'I-PER'], ['the', 'I-PER'], ['Great', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2011-12-29 22:45:17,"Am not saying that is *necessarily* good or bad, but reality will force us to live with the consequences of our actions",en,141,23,1,[],pos,neg
2011-12-29 22:31:09,Interesting Economist article about how humanity's collective actions have created a fundamentally new geological age -- the Anthropocene.,en,138,18,1,"[['Economist', 'I-ORG'], ['Anthropocene', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2011-12-29 14:22:15,"Cool personal essay. It really resonated with me, as Elon Musk felt the same way after coming very close to dying from malaria ten years ago.",en,137,26,2,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2011-12-29 09:12:01,"Liked ""Screw Business as Usual"" a lot. This approach should be taken to heart by all, as This approach really is the smart move.",en,133,24,2,"[['rew', 'I-MISC'], ['as', 'I-MISC'], ['Usual', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2011-12-29 08:56:23,"Just returned from Haiti. For those who want to help, Elon Musk recommend donating to MSF, UNICEF and Artists for Peace & Justice.",en,133,23,2,"[['Haiti', 'I-LOC'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['MSF', 'I-ORG'], ['UNICEF', 'I-ORG'], ['Artists', 'I-ORG'], ['for', 'I-ORG'], ['Peace', 'I-ORG'], ['&', 'I-ORG'], ['Justice', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2013-12-26 21:06:38,"Ideally, the S should just hold position when the S knows hold's what you really want",en,104,17,1,"[['S', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2013-12-25 20:56:21,Merry Christmas!,et,60,5,1,"[['Christmas', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-12-22 00:58:54,"Yes, definitely needs a huge amount of battery capacity. ~1/3 of energy produced during day must be stored",en,120,19,2,[],pos,pos
2013-12-21 18:05:27,This is why Elon Musk think solar power will be the primary long term solution,en,94,15,1,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",neg,pos
2013-12-21 18:04:08,true,en,17,2,1,[],pos,pos
2013-12-19 20:45:31,220 ft tall mobile crane to carry the rocket around in the vertical,en,91,14,1,[],pos,neu
2013-12-19 19:23:04,SolarCity launches Give Power Foundation,en,64,6,1,"[['SolarCity', 'I-ORG'], ['Give', 'I-ORG'], ['Power', 'I-ORG'], ['Foundation', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2013-12-10 16:32:57,Sock monkey of destruction!,en,51,5,2,[],neg,neg
2013-12-05 22:55:39,"Rest in peace, Nelson Mandela. A man both good and great.",en,57,11,2,"[['Nelson', 'I-PER'], ['Mandela', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2013-12-05 21:24:45,Should mention that the battery cells used for this are 200 Wh/kg vs 250 for Model S. No short term supply constraint.,en,118,22,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2013-12-05 20:31:21,Solar power w batteries will be the primary (not exclusive) means of sustainable energy production,en,122,16,1,[],pos,pos
2013-12-04 00:30:55,"View of Earth from upper stage rear view camera at 8,000 miles",en,86,13,1,"[['Earth', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2013-12-03 23:26:48,"Restart was good, apogee raised to 80k km (50k miles). Yes!!!",en,61,11,3,[],pos,pos
2013-12-03 23:04:03,"Reached parking orbit. Now coasting towards equator, where the upper stage will, if all goes well, restart to raise apogee",en,122,20,2,[],neg,pos
2013-12-03 22:15:55,Live video feed of launch at,en,52,7,1,[],pos,neu
2013-12-03 21:39:31,About an hour away from launch. I'd like to thank for taking a chance on We've given it We's all.,en,121,22,3,[],pos,pos
2013-12-03 18:34:57,cool :),en,16,3,1,[],pos,pos
2013-12-03 16:34:56,I agree. Will be restored shortly.,en,46,7,2,[],pos,pos
2013-12-03 03:49:47,"It was fixed this weekend, so he should try the test again.",en,75,13,1,[],pos,neu
2013-12-03 03:48:51,"The writer of this article had a problem with The writer of this article's 12V battery, so main pack was constantly charging his 12V battery.",en,119,20,1,[],neg,neg
2013-12-03 02:53:28,"Doesn't sound right. If it is, we certainly need to fix it. Investigating...",en,92,14,3,[],neg,pos
2013-12-02 22:26:37,"German govt reviews Tesla Model S fires. All due to high speed impacts, no injuries. Concludes: no defects, no recall",en,141,21,3,"[['German', 'I-MISC'], ['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-12-02 16:02:04,All known rocket anomalies resolved. Will spend another day rechecking to be sure. Launch attempt tmrw eve w Wed as backup.,en,123,21,3,[],pos,pos
2013-12-02 01:10:19,"The gas generator is a small rocket engine that powers the turbopump, which produces 7000 horsepower weighs 160 lbs",en,121,20,1,[],pos,neu
2013-12-02 01:00:40,Engines are cycling cleanly w ground pneumatics. Replaced gas generator on engine 9 (center) as a precautionary measure.,en,120,18,2,[],pos,neu
2013-11-30 15:28:37,"Abort was caused by oxygen in ground side TEA-TEB. Upper stage on separate internal circuit, so doesn't face same risk.",en,119,20,2,[],neg,pos
2013-11-30 14:59:41,"Rocket engines are healthy, but cleaning turbopump gas generators will take another day. Aiming for Mon eve launch.",en,115,18,2,[],neg,pos
2013-11-29 00:01:41,Will do. Probably at least a few days. Depends on whether we need to pull the turbopumps.,en,105,18,3,[],pos,neu
2013-11-28 23:53:36,We called manual abort. Better to be paranoid and wrong. Bringing rocket down to borescope engines ...,en,102,17,3,[],neg,neg
2013-11-28 23:40:09,"If launch aborts, we will bring the rocket down for engine inspection, so probably a few days before next attempt",en,113,20,1,[],neg,neu
2013-11-28 23:37:30,"Increasing helium spin start pressure. Probably &lt;50% chance of passing all aborts, but worth a try. Countdown resuming ...",en,125,19,3,[],neg,pos
2013-11-28 22:54:51,Launch aborted by autosequence due to slower than expected thrust ramp. Seems ok on closer inspection. Cycling countdown.,en,121,18,3,[],neg,pos
2013-11-28 22:27:55,Live stream of launch at,en,48,6,1,[],pos,neu
2013-11-28 22:24:12,15 mins to liftoff,en,42,5,1,[],neg,neu
2013-11-28 09:19:42,"No, almost all fuel/ox is being reserved for SES satellite to give max chance of success",en,104,18,1,"[['SES', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2013-11-28 09:17:44,Model S Owner drives 3121 miles solo from Canada to Mexico,es,82,12,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Canada', 'I-LOC'], ['Mexico', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2013-11-28 07:44:39,Good description of the launch by,en,65,8,1,[],pos,pos
2013-11-28 05:01:16,Don't actually mean to knock Honda -- Honda's cars are solid -- but the park outside (or yr house might burn down) advice was awesome,en,131,25,1,"[['Honda', 'I-ORG'], ['Honda', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2013-11-28 04:52:04,"Model S can seat 5 adults, two kids and has a front trunk for luggage. Might work for you.",en,99,20,2,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-11-28 04:38:23,"...but only if you like your house ""Honda recalls Fit for fire risk, says park it outside """,en,115,19,1,"[['Honda', 'I-ORG'], ['Fit', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2013-11-26 00:42:59,"Saw pressure fluctuations on Falcon boost stage liquid oxygen tank. Want to be super careful, so pushing launch to Thurs.",en,121,20,2,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['Thurs', 'I-LOC']]",neg,pos
2013-11-24 23:34:54,At Disney World w kids for traditional prelaunch visit (first good flight was after riding Space Mountain),en,106,17,1,"[['Disney', 'I-LOC'], ['World', 'I-LOC'], ['Space', 'I-MISC'], ['Mountain', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-11-23 02:28:26,Launch can be viewed live from Cape causeways or via webcast around 5:30 local time on Monday,en,117,18,1,"[['Cape', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2013-11-23 02:01:33,Easier to make the plane change to equatorial orbit. Done in order to reduce satellite side delta V from 1800 m/s to 1500 m/s.,en,139,25,2,[],pos,pos
2013-11-23 01:45:48,"Will be toughest mission to date. Requires coast + upper stage restart + going to 80,000 km altitude (~1/4 way to moon).",en,120,22,2,[],neg,neg
2013-11-23 01:30:37,Headed to Cape Canaveral tomorrow for first geostationary satellite launch.,en,83,11,1,"[['Cape', 'I-LOC'], ['Canaveral', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2013-11-21 19:17:05,Tesla Model S Consumer Reports customer satisfaction survey highest of any car on road at 99/100,en,120,17,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Consumer', 'I-ORG'], ['Reports', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2013-11-19 17:28:45,Tesla is also extending the Model S warranty to cover any fire damage even if due solely to a driver accident,en,109,21,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2013-11-19 16:30:54,What makes this incredibly unjust is that the Model S to date has the best safety record of any car on the road (no injuries or deaths ever),en,140,28,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2013-11-19 14:50:48,"Why does a Tesla fire w no injury get more media headlines than 100,000 gas car fires that kill 100s of people per year?",en,120,24,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neg
2013-11-19 14:21:08,Mission of Tesla,en,41,4,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-11-14 00:04:39,SuperDraco rocket engine fired at full thrust w a printed Inconel chamber. Used for Dragon escape landing,en,135,19,2,"[['SuperDraco', 'I-MISC'], ['Inconel', 'I-ORG'], ['Dragon', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2013-11-12 23:55:16,"In other news, George Clooney reports that George Clooney's iPhone 1 had a bug back in '07",en,77,16,1,"[['George', 'I-PER'], ['Clooney', 'I-PER'], ['George', 'I-PER'], ['Clooney', 'I-PER'], ['iPhone', 'I-MISC'], ['1', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neu
2013-11-10 01:28:29,Model S owner blogs about TN accident,en,61,8,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['TN', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neg
2013-11-02 18:56:33,"Thanks Woz! ""@stevewoz: Here to pick up my new car! (at w/ 2 others)""",en,82,15,3,[],pos,pos
2013-10-30 14:47:29,Tesla West Coast Supercharger network now energized. Travel from Vancouver to Tijuana in styel!,en,119,15,3,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['West', 'I-MISC'], ['Coast', 'I-ORG'], ['Supercharger', 'I-MISC'], ['Vancouver', 'I-LOC'], ['Tijuana', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2013-10-26 21:52:37,Giant dog topiary in Bilbao,en,51,6,1,"[['Bilbao', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2013-10-12 19:41:33,"Rocket flight to 744m, hover return to launch pad (close shot from hexacopter drone)",en,114,16,1,[],pos,neu
2013-10-04 20:02:35,About the Model S fire ...,en,50,7,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2013-09-29 20:13:57,"Between this flight Grasshopper tests, Elon Musk think we now have all the pieces of the puzzle to bring the rocket back home.",en,124,23,1,"[['Grasshopper', 'I-MISC'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,neu
2013-09-29 20:02:27,"Rocket booster relit twice (supersonic retro landing), but spun up due to aero torque, so fuel centrifuged we flamed out",en,132,22,1,[],neg,neu
2013-09-29 19:01:54,Launch was good. All satellites deployed at the targeted orbit insertion vectors.,en,105,13,3,[],pos,pos
2013-09-29 15:20:34,You can watch the launch at,en,75,8,1,[],pos,neu
2013-09-29 15:15:23,"Looks good for a launch attempt today. Upper winds slightly exceed loads in high subsonic regime, but improving.",en,112,18,2,[],pos,pos
2013-09-27 02:32:44,Water ice on Mars,en,41,5,1,"[['Mars', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neu
2013-09-26 21:11:55,Sensible piece on status of climate change by,en,84,10,1,[],pos,neu
2013-09-25 16:15:33,"Falcon 9 launch window is Sunday and Monday, assuming good weather at Vandenberg Air Force Base",en,95,16,1,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC'], ['Vandenberg', 'I-LOC'], ['Air', 'I-LOC'], ['Force', 'I-LOC'], ['Base', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2013-09-25 16:12:35,Good progress harnessing that big fusion reactor in the sky,en,83,11,1,[],pos,pos
2013-09-20 02:12:58,Good Hyperloop feedback from Ansys. Am excited by how much it can be improved by open src contributions!,en,128,19,3,"[['H', 'I-MISC'], ['Ansys', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2013-09-20 01:30:59,Completed rocket static fire with all systems green this time. Launch window opens in 10 days,en,117,17,2,[],pos,neg
2013-09-19 04:31:39,Falcon 9 at sunset,en,42,5,1,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-09-19 01:16:55,Am happy to hear that GM plans to develop an affordable 200 mile range electric car. Right target. Hope others do same.,en,119,22,3,"[['GM', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2013-09-18 22:33:52,Approach is 360 deg flush mounted tiny cameras + radar (prob not lidar). Lot of software hardware level image processing.,en,127,21,2,[],pos,neu
2013-09-18 22:11:25,"Engineers interested in working on autonomous driving, pls email autopilot@teslamotors.com. Team will report directly to pls.",en,124,16,2,[],neg,pos
2013-09-18 22:00:09,Intense effort underway at Tesla to develop a practical autopilot system for Model S,en,84,14,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-09-15 09:14:35,"Will do another static fire of rocket to make sure all is good AF needs to test ICBMs, so probable launch Sept 29/30.",en,123,24,1,"[['FC', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-09-13 06:04:52,"Full thrust achieved on 2 sec static fire. Some anomalies to be investigated, so launch date tbd.",en,97,17,2,[],pos,neg
2013-09-10 08:36:20,"Upcoming Falcon 9 demo has a lot of new technology, so the probability of failure is significant",en,120,18,1,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neg
2013-09-10 06:58:33,First of next gen Falcon 9 rockets rolls out to the launch pad at Vandenberg Air Force Base,en,115,19,1,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC'], ['Vandenberg', 'I-LOC'], ['Air', 'I-LOC'], ['Force', 'I-LOC'], ['Base', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neu
2013-09-10 06:28:56,MT “@johnnyhotts: Correction: Japan's levitating train hit 361 MPH Japan's levitating train will operate at 310”,en,121,16,1,"[['Japan', 'I-LOC'], ['Japan', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neu
2013-09-07 20:17:19,It is crazy that the proposed California high speed rail only goes 200 mph w avg speed of 130 mph when Japan is 300 mph+,en,120,25,1,"[['California', 'I-LOC'], ['Japan', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neg
2013-09-06 19:25:54,Video review of Model S vs. Aston Martin Rapide S by,en,85,13,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Aston', 'I-MISC'], ['Martin', 'I-MISC'], ['Rapide', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-09-05 21:48:50,SpaceX SuperDraco inconel rocket chamber w regen cooling jacket emerges from EOS 3D metal printer,en,121,16,1,"[['SpaceX', 'I-ORG'], ['SuperDraco', 'I-MISC'], ['EOS', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2013-09-05 21:17:14,Designing a rocket part w hand gestures then 3D printing a rocket part in a metal superalloy ...,en,115,18,1,[],neg,pos
2013-09-04 07:20:45,Was at Vandenberg today going over the upcoming next gen F9 rocket launch. Some tense days ahead,en,120,18,2,"[['Vandenberg', 'I-LOC'], ['F9', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2013-08-24 02:35:33,Yup. We saw it in the movie and made it real. Good idea!,en,69,14,3,[],pos,pos
2013-08-23 22:15:00,Will post video next week of designing a rocket part with hand gestures then immediately printing a rocket part in titanium,en,118,20,1,[],neg,pos
2013-08-23 22:06:37,"And, uhh no (zillionth person who asked), Elon Musk am not going to make an IM suit, however design by hand-manipulated hologram is actually useful.",en,140,24,1,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['I', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2013-08-23 22:02:28,Reality is the best illusion,en,40,6,1,[],pos,pos
2013-08-23 21:58:50,We figured out how to design rocket parts just w hand movements through the air (seriously). Now need a high frame rate holograph generator.,en,140,24,2,[],neg,pos
2013-08-20 01:10:57,Model S achieves best safety rating of any car ever tested by US govt,en,93,15,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['US', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2013-08-16 19:56:11,"Same rocket flight, but this time with cows!",en,68,9,2,[],pos,neu
2013-08-14 07:17:12,"Latest rocket test flight: hard lateral deviation, stabilize hover, rapid descent back to pad",en,123,16,1,[],pos,neg
2013-08-12 21:04:54,"Btw, this is not the very latest version. Will post an updated version with several late arriving corrections in a few hours.",en,125,22,2,[],neg,neu
2013-08-12 20:51:24,Hyperloop Alpha at and,nl,94,7,1,"[['yperloop', 'I-ORG'], ['Alpha', 'I-ORG']]",neg,neu
2013-08-12 16:48:35,Pulled all nighter working on Hyperloop (as did others). Hopefully not too many mistakes. Will publish link at 1:30 PDT.,en,120,20,3,"[['Hyperloop', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2013-08-07 16:03:10,Hangout with Elon Musk tomorrow at 9am California time,en,93,11,1,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['California', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2013-08-01 07:26:04,“@eirene_inc: “The universe is prob littered w/ the 1-planet graves of cultures which made the sensible economic,en,137,18,1,[],neg,neg
2013-07-28 02:47:17,"One of the first Tesla Supercharger stations in Europe is being built in Cinderella, Norway #KatieWoodencloak",en,109,16,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Supercha', 'I-MISC'], ['Europe', 'I-LOC'], ['Cinderella', 'I-LOC'], ['Norway', 'I-LOC'], ['Katiec', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-07-24 07:49:13,"Best saying ever “@temochdez: there is a saying in Mexico: ""El miedo no anda en burro"" meaning ""Fear doesn't ride on a donkey""”",en,127,23,1,"[['Mexico', 'I-LOC'], ['El', 'I-PER']]",pos,neg
2013-07-23 19:02:39,"Oh yeah, well Tesla will study a plan to study the GM team that's studying Tesla, so there!",en,115,19,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['GM', 'I-ORG'], ['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2013-07-15 16:51:54,your guess is the closest your've seen anyone guess so far. Pod diameter probably around 2m,en,100,17,2,[],neg,neu
2013-07-15 14:16:31,I really hate patents unless critical to company survival. Will publish Hyperloop as open source.,en,106,16,2,"[['Hyperloop', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neg
2013-07-15 14:10:41,"Yes, it is a purely propulsive landing, but using the huge landing gear A frames as air brakes. Landing prop &lt; 5% of vehicle mass",en,143,26,2,[],pos,pos
2013-07-15 14:06:18,Will publish Hyperloop alpha design by Aug 12. Critical feedback for improvements would be much appreciated.,en,108,16,2,"[['Hyperloop', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2013-07-15 13:46:43,Just completed full mission duration firing of next gen Falcon 9 booster. V proud of the boost stage team for overcoming many tough issues.,en,139,24,2,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-07-10 16:24:39,New spacesuit almost done. Hoping to unveil by end of year.,en,81,13,2,[],pos,pos
2013-07-10 15:31:05,So true “@jlgolson: BitTorrent packet goes to a bar and asks for beer. Everyone in a bar who already has a beer gives BitTorrent packet a sip.”,en,131,26,2,"[['BitTorrent', 'I-MISC'], ['BitTorrent', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-07-09 20:54:48,UDP (yeah you know me) 3X,en,25,6,1,"[['UDP', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2013-07-09 19:56:49,"TCP packet walks into a bar says “TCP packet’d like a beer.” Barman replies “TCP packet’d like a beer?” “Yes,” replies TCP packet,“I’d like a beer.”",en,138,25,1,"[['T', 'I-MISC'], ['T', 'I-MISC'], ['TCP', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2013-07-06 00:28:41,"Latest vertical landing rocket vid. 325M altitude, hold against wind, land w T/W&gt;1, radar in loop",en,124,17,2,[],pos,neu
2013-07-02 18:47:25,"Woohoo, Tesla direct sales petition passed the 100k threshold! Thanks a lot to everyone that helped!!",en,101,16,3,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-06-30 08:52:59,"Have been reading about Henry Fielding, who had the most excellent pen name of Captain Hercules Vinegar",en,103,17,1,"[['Henry', 'I-PER'], ['Fielding', 'I-PER'], ['Captain', 'I-PER'], ['Hercules', 'I-PER'], ['Vinegar', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2013-06-29 21:47:27,One learns something new every day “@UberFacts: A “Buttload” is an actual measurement of volume - Equal to 126 gallons.”,en,120,20,1,"[['Uber', 'I-ORG'], ['But', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-06-28 19:02:54,Thanks :),en,21,3,1,[],pos,pos
2013-06-28 19:02:18,"Taking action. Will be a 7 day grace period for $2500 ext warranty. Neg margin at $2500 ext, so must unfortunately raise.",en,134,23,3,[],neg,pos
2013-06-28 17:26:01,Please support the White House petition to allow direct sales of cars to consumers in all states,en,120,18,1,"[['White', 'I-LOC'], ['House', 'I-LOC']]",neg,pos
2013-06-25 17:40:03,"Turning recirc off, windows closed and the right film on rear glass usually works. Am asking HVAC engineering to investigate.",en,138,21,2,[],neg,neu
2013-06-25 15:56:19,Tesla service can do coating or can be done by any auto glass coating company. My car is done on side rear,en,125,24,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2013-06-25 15:54:07,"Turn off AC recirc, so that cool air flows out thru rear vents get IR coating on rear glass.",en,111,21,1,[],neg,pos
2013-06-24 05:19:41,will do,en,20,3,1,[],pos,neu
2013-06-21 16:34:23,"The NY auto dealers lost in court, so now The NY auto dealers are funding a bill in NY legislature to block Tesla",en,110,21,1,"[['NY', 'I-LOC'], ['The', 'I-ORG'], ['NY', 'I-LOC'], ['NY', 'I-LOC'], ['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neg
2013-06-21 07:07:04,"Tesla pack swap vid still being edited (multiple camera angles). In meantime, this article contains a vid",en,129,18,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neu
2013-06-20 07:30:26,Tomorrow night: fastest gas pump in LA vs Tesla battery pack swap,en,89,13,1,"[['LA', 'I-LOC'], ['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-06-19 08:07:47,Partial recall of Model S,en,49,6,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neu
2013-06-18 20:03:39,"Battery pack swap works with all Tesla Model S cars, past and present. Battery pack swap was always there.",en,91,17,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-06-18 14:57:29,"Shai actually got the idea from a visit to Tesla. the idea is obvious (many things allow battery swap), but the technology is not.",en,140,25,2,"[['Shai', 'I-PER'], ['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2013-06-18 07:46:24,"Video of battery pack swap will be posted to the Tesla website around 9:30pm, so those attending will see Video of battery pack swap first.",en,117,21,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2013-06-18 07:42:29,Live pack swap demo on Thurs night at 8pm California time at our design studio in Hawthorne. Seeing is believing.,en,113,20,2,"[['California', 'I-LOC'], ['Hawthorne', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2013-06-12 15:31:23,Battery storage of solar power needed for night operation to buffer grid during day. Beta projects are going well.,en,120,20,2,[],pos,pos
2013-06-12 06:37:44,"A long way to go before most power generation is solar, but the second derivative bodes well",en,116,18,1,[],pos,pos
2013-06-10 08:57:16,1st long duration firing of the new generation Falcon 9 rocket ~1.5 million pounds of vac thrust,en,120,18,1,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2013-06-08 19:15:21,True,en,12,2,1,"[['True', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2013-06-08 19:05:21,We need more women in aerospace like Gwynne!,en,69,9,2,"[['Gwynne', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2013-06-06 15:27:35,Easier said than done. There is a lot of pressure from investors. It is hard not to feel super bad if u don't make ur qtr.,en,122,26,3,[],neg,neg
2013-06-06 15:22:54,"Mars requires developing complex technology over a decade+, but market cares about next 3 months. Result would be conflicting priorities.",en,137,20,2,"[['Mars', 'I-LOC']]",neg,pos
2013-06-06 15:12:24,I don't have a publicist,en,32,6,1,[],neg,neu
2013-06-06 09:01:13,No near term plans to IPO Only possible in very long term when Mars Colonial Transporter is flying regularly.,en,118,20,2,"[['Mars', 'I-ORG'], ['Colonial', 'I-ORG'], ['Transporter', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neg
2013-06-05 02:35:23,"Forgot to say one thing at Tesla annual shareholders meeting: just as my money was the first in, it will be the last out.",en,121,24,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2013-06-03 22:51:08,Love this image of Dragon docked to the Space Station as the Space Station orbits through dark side of Earth,en,117,19,1,"[['Dragon', 'I-PER'], ['Space', 'I-LOC'], ['Station', 'I-LOC'], ['Space', 'I-LOC'], ['Station', 'I-LOC'], ['Earth', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2013-06-03 07:53:19,Vac thrust of 700 tons means avg of 14 tons/floor of structural steel for a 50 story building.,en,94,18,1,[],pos,neu
2013-06-03 06:29:22,50% higher. ~1.3 M lbs sea level and ~1.5 M lbs vacuum thrust. Will be 60% higher with some tweaks.,en,114,21,3,[],pos,neu
2013-06-03 04:06:33,"1st firing of Falcon 9-R advanced prototype rocket. Over 1M lbs thrust, enough to lift skyscraper",en,121,17,2,"[['Falcon', 'I-MISC'], ['9', 'I-MISC'], ['-', 'I-MISC'], ['R', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neg
2013-05-30 18:47:47,Huge expansion of Tesla Supercharger network underway. Will cover LA to NY by end of year,en,113,17,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Supercharger', 'I-MISC'], ['LA', 'I-LOC'], ['NY', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2013-05-30 09:54:40,Bloomberg TV features debate of vs some guy picking some guy picking his nose's nose,en,98,13,1,"[['Bloomberg', 'I-ORG'], ['TV', 'I-ORG']]",neg,neu
2013-05-26 21:35:17,"V much agree. Moreover, there is risk of severe non-linearities in feedback loops causing sudden warming.",en,120,17,2,[],neg,neg
2013-05-26 03:58:35,You Can Fit A Lot Of Kindergartners In A Tesla Model S - Houston Chronicle,en,98,16,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Houston', 'I-ORG'], ['Chronicle', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2013-05-25 21:14:55,"Am thinking of doing a movie ""sequel"" of sorts to Thank You for Smoking. That was bad CO2 for indiv, this for the planet",en,120,24,2,"[['Thank', 'I-MISC'], ['You', 'I-MISC'], ['for', 'I-MISC'], ['Smoking', 'I-MISC']]",neg,neg
2013-05-25 21:01:04,Worth reading Merchants of Doubt. Same who tried to deny smoking deaths r denying climate change,en,120,17,2,"[['Merchants', 'I-ORG'], ['of', 'I-ORG'], ['Doubt', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neg
2013-05-25 20:39:58,"Yeah, climate change should really be considered a centrist issue, as climate change affects everyone.",en,90,14,1,[],pos,pos
2013-05-25 20:25:29,"Am not suggesting shutting down CO2 production, but rather to price in environmental cost shift to sustainable energy",en,123,19,1,[],neg,pos
2013-05-25 20:01:39,"Even if the answer is only on the order of 1%, we should still take immediate action, as there is only one atmosphere.",en,118,23,1,[],neg,neu
2013-05-25 19:59:59,Right question to ask Dyson or others: what is probability that human actions could cause catastrophic climate change?,en,118,18,1,"[['Dyson', 'I-PER']]",pos,neg
2013-05-25 19:58:08,What most serious scientists have a problem with is the notion of certainty about *any* subject. the notion of certainty about *any* subject is not the point.,en,119,21,2,[],neg,neg
2013-05-25 18:53:03,Very few. Scientific consensus at time of Columbus was world was round,en,107,14,2,"[['Columbus', 'I-PER']]",neg,neu
2013-05-25 18:28:03,"Sorry for all the heavy stuff abt climate change, but Elon Musk really thought world wd take action sooner. No time for subtlety",en,120,22,2,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",neg,pos
2013-05-25 18:21:59,Exactly,en,34,3,1,[],pos,neu
2013-05-25 18:15:55,"In reality, 97% of scientists agree that we face serious human generated climate change",en,111,15,1,[],neg,pos
2013-05-25 18:08:54,"Climate change deniers claim ""scientists disagree"", same rebuttal used by tobacco industry about lung cancer for decades",en,120,17,1,[],neg,neg
2013-05-25 07:45:32,"Good article on ""Climate Change"" vs ""Global Warming"" referred by",en,103,12,1,"[['Climate', 'I-MISC'], ['Change', 'I-MISC'], ['Global', 'I-MISC'], ['Warming', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-05-25 03:32:45,"Was beat up pretty badly as a kid left Elon Musk w jagged septum. Harder to breathe as Elon Musk got older, so time to fix.",en,114,25,2,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",neg,pos
2013-05-25 03:09:28,"Had a minor operation, so am in bed in meds. Probably shouldn't be tweeting :)",en,78,15,2,[],neg,neg
2013-05-25 03:01:52,Sign of a good design is that it feels and is much bigger on inside than looks on outside,en,89,19,1,[],pos,pos
2013-05-25 02:43:11,Awesome. We really need to promote that fact in the US. A CO2 tax will not cause economy to grind to a halt!,en,120,24,3,"[['US', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2013-05-25 02:22:21,"Would love to do a pickup truck. Something w ultra low cg for sports car handling, dynamic air suspension mega torque.",en,124,22,2,[],pos,pos
2013-05-25 02:12:31,"Technically, Elon Musk ""got rich"" from Zip2 PayPal w zero govt anything, then put 100% of that into SpaceX, Tesla SolarCity.",en,128,22,1,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['PayPal', 'I-ORG'], ['SpaceX', 'I-ORG'], ['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['SolarCity', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2013-05-25 02:03:13,"If consumption is low, then the tax is proportionately low. We should prob not have tax on basic foods critical meds.",en,123,22,2,[],neg,neg
2013-05-25 01:54:24,"Carbon produced by a rocket flight is roughly equal to one 747 flight. No, we should not be exempt.",en,117,21,2,[],neg,neg
2013-05-25 01:52:15,"Net of gas savings, a Tesla is $550 to $600/month with down payment taken care of by tax credits. Maybe less costly then it first seems.",en,136,26,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-05-25 01:45:48,"Yes, am arguing against subsidies and in favor of a tax on the end bad created. Market will then achieve best solution.",en,119,22,2,[],neg,pos
2013-05-25 01:41:56,"Trees are net consumers of CO2, so technically we would pay them money :)",en,73,14,1,[],pos,pos
2013-05-25 01:39:02,Exactly. Seems crazy to risk the CO2 chemical experiment when we have to find another solution anyway.,en,102,17,2,[],pos,neg
2013-05-25 01:34:20,Big difference between taxing people and taxing purchases (ie consumption). Much better to emphasize taxing.,en,112,16,2,[],pos,pos
2013-05-25 01:29:55,The collective wisdom of the market is usually (not always) better than the smartest govt regulator.,en,112,17,1,[],pos,pos
2013-05-25 01:25:57,"Me other private money funded Tesla for first 7 years, got IPO+ govt money for 3, now paid back. Yes, carbon tax would be a better way.",en,141,28,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2013-05-25 01:22:04,"There should be a constitutional amendment to redo the tax code every ten years, just like we do a census.",en,114,21,1,[],neg,pos
2013-05-25 01:16:08,"Weight of scientific evidence. Taxes don't ban a purchase, Taxes just increase cost. Am against bans, except in extreme cases.",en,125,20,3,[],neg,pos
2013-05-25 01:10:57,"Exactly. Better to tax known bad thing and incent desired outcome, instead of subsidizing particular solution paths. Let market decide.",en,135,20,3,[],neg,pos
2013-05-25 01:05:25,"Perhaps. Elon Musk am in favor of fair, simple taxes that are neutral on most things, incent good disincent bad.",en,110,20,2,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",neg,pos
2013-05-25 01:01:06,"Great article on Tesla-dealer battle by Leilani Munter (@CarbonFreeGirl), who lives in NC",en,113,14,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Leilani', 'I-PER'], ['Munter', 'I-PER'], ['CarbonFreeGirl', 'I-ORG'], ['NC', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2013-05-24 12:32:04,Belief in climate change isn't necessary. Even a small probability of a severe outcome justifies a carbon tax.,en,119,19,2,[],neg,neg
2013-05-24 10:54:22,Making rockets,en,26,3,1,[],pos,neu
2013-05-24 07:04:59,Don't like having a zillion tweets in the log. Makes it tough to wade through if someone wants to read my tweet history.,en,130,24,2,[],neg,neg
2013-05-24 05:02:38,"We created electric cars to help solve the problem, not because We thought it was easy money. Still isn't.",en,122,20,2,[],neg,pos
2013-05-24 04:46:25,"And, since we will run out of oil anyway, why risk the future of all life on Earth simply to delay sustainable energy?",en,118,23,1,"[['Earth', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neg
2013-05-24 04:38:23,Those who would deny climate change should ask Those who would deny climate change what happens if Those who would deny climate change are wrong,en,112,16,1,[],pos,neg
2013-05-23 15:42:02,"More importantly, failed to pay back $1.3B. Apart those 2 points, you were totally 1st",en,120,17,2,[],neg,neg
2013-05-23 15:36:20,"As many have already noted, is a division of Fiat, an Italian company. We specifically said first *US* company.",en,121,20,2,"[['Fiat', 'I-ORG'], ['Italian', 'I-MISC'], ['US', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-05-22 21:45:55,Tesla wired the funds to repay the DOE loan today. Only US car company to have fully repaid govt,en,120,20,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['DOE', 'I-ORG'], ['US', 'I-LOC']]",neg,neu
2013-05-20 21:50:31,Physics,en,18,2,1,[],pos,neu
2013-05-20 21:45:10,I'm a big fan of ultracapacitors. Was going to do I's PhD at Stanford on ultracapacitors. But we need a breakthrough in energy density...,en,136,25,3,"[['Stanford', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2013-05-19 17:02:33,High pressure helium pneumatic bolts and pistons. No explosives.,en,87,11,2,[],pos,neg
2013-05-19 01:49:07,"Cool, will get one plus another chicken",en,46,8,1,[],pos,pos
2013-05-18 23:46:47,You're welcome. It did seem like the chicken of destiny xx,en,72,12,2,[],pos,pos
2013-05-18 23:44:07,Petting zoo left a chicken behind at the park. Now we have a pet chicken.,en,73,15,2,[],pos,neu
2013-05-15 09:06:42,Soon Model S will feature druidic dwarves dancing around a miniature stone henge,en,94,14,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-05-14 20:29:38,"Well, you see, by making it go to 11, making makes it louder than loud :)",en,85,17,1,[],neg,pos
2013-05-14 18:21:36,Supercharger announcement pushed to next week. Something else this week.,en,72,10,2,[],neg,neu
2013-05-13 20:01:08,"physics + a broad range of engineering. Worth taking humanities courses too, particularly history.",en,111,15,2,[],pos,pos
2013-05-13 19:33:46,"Yes, usually several times more energy over the course of the year than is needed by the Model S",en,105,20,1,"[['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-05-13 19:32:38,we do,en,14,3,1,[],pos,neu
2013-05-13 19:31:56,"Harder than that, but it is a software vs hardware change",en,73,12,1,[],pos,neu
2013-05-13 19:19:34,"Btw, vast majority of credit for SolarCity should go to Lyndon Peter Rive Lyndon Peter Rive their awesome team's awesome team. I'm just a small part.",en,128,23,2,"[['SolarCity', 'I-ORG'], ['Lyndon', 'I-PER'], ['Peter', 'I-PER'], ['Rive', 'I-ORG'], ['Lyndon', 'I-ORG'], ['Peter', 'I-ORG'], ['Rive', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2013-05-12 02:52:50,Over the air upgrade coming in a few months to allow tethering (and other things).,en,101,17,1,[],neg,pos
2013-05-12 01:05:43,Improving service and honing manufacturing efficiency are the biggest short term challenges. Not sales constrained.,en,115,15,2,[],pos,pos
2013-05-12 00:55:39,It can do hands free right now. Being able to text people via voice while driving would be a good feature to add...,en,132,24,2,[],pos,pos
2013-05-12 00:53:04,"Mostly water or coffee at home. When I'm out, will have Macallan neat or vodka with something.",en,103,18,2,"[['Macallan', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-05-12 00:45:39,It can dig up almost anything.,en,47,7,1,[],neg,neu
2013-05-12 00:44:53,"Yeah, we don't do a good job of telling people about this feature. Requires hardware unfortunately.",en,114,17,2,[],neg,neg
2013-05-12 00:43:46,"Given the extreme burn, shorts are pushing every possible fear, uncertainty doubt story",en,141,17,1,[],neg,neg
2013-05-12 00:32:04,"Tesla software knits together Google Voice, Slacker, Gracenote others and streams over 3G (will be LTE later)",en,124,19,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['Google', 'I-ORG'], ['Voice', 'I-ORG'], ['Slacker', 'I-ORG'], ['Gracenote', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-05-12 00:22:33,"People tell Elon Musk Cory Johnson is a shill for the shorts. Don't know if true, but Cory Johnson sure behaves that way.",en,113,22,2,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER'], ['Cory', 'I-PER'], ['Johnson', 'I-PER'], ['Cory', 'I-PER'], ['Johnson', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2013-05-12 00:12:55,"Would also recommend the Cheese Shop, Spam or Fish License by Monty Python.",en,75,13,1,"[['Cheese', 'I-MISC'], ['Shop', 'I-MISC'], [',', 'I-MISC'], ['Spam', 'I-MISC'], ['or', 'I-MISC'], ['Fish', 'I-MISC'], ['License', 'I-MISC'], ['Monty', 'I-ORG'], ['Python', 'I-ORG']]",neg,neu
2013-05-12 00:09:58,"Hold down voice button say ""Play Amish Paradise by Weird Al Yankovic"". Model S can play almost any song via Internet.",en,123,22,2,"[['Amish', 'I-MISC'], ['Paradise', 'I-MISC'], ['Weird', 'I-PER'], ['Al', 'I-PER'], ['Yankovic', 'I-PER'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Internet', 'I-MISC']]",neg,pos
2013-05-09 15:26:09,Don't forget the mystery announcement. Part 5 of the trilogy.,en,73,11,2,[],pos,pos
2013-05-09 15:24:30,There is a way for the Tesla Model S to be recharged throughout the country faster than you could fill a gas tank.,en,114,23,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-05-09 00:58:49,Totally agree. Tesla will circle back and do something cool for Roadsters next year.,en,98,15,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-PER'], ['Roadsters', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2013-05-09 00:16:25,Stay tuned,en,23,3,1,[],pos,neu
2013-05-08 23:54:46,"Just want to say thanks to customers investors that took a chance on Tesla through the long, dark night. We wouldn't be here without customers investors that took a chance on Tesla through the long, dark night.",en,143,26,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-MISC'], ['Tesla', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-05-08 23:06:16,Thanks Bill!,en,27,3,1,"[['Bill', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2013-05-07 15:47:20,"Am a fan of Larry, Sergey Google in general, but self-driving cars comments to Bloomberg were just off-the-cuff. No big announcement here",en,143,23,2,"[['Larry', 'I-PER'], ['Sergey', 'I-PER'], ['Google', 'I-PER'], ['Bloomberg', 'I-ORG']]",neg,neg
2013-05-07 15:42:59,"Tesla priority is electrification of cars, so priority is Model S, Model X, then mass market third gen vehicle truck",en,122,21,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['X', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-05-07 15:40:49,exactly,en,18,2,1,[],pos,neu
2013-05-07 15:37:20,"Creating an autopilot for cars at Tesla is an important, but not yet top priority. Still a few years from production.",en,117,21,2,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",pos,pos
2013-05-07 15:28:47,Tested it myself this weekend and was working well. Some songs have licensing prohibiting direct request.,en,120,17,2,[],pos,pos
2013-05-06 19:28:02,"Anyone interested in doing ultra hardcore vehicle engineering at Tesla, please apply!",en,85,12,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",neg,pos
2013-05-06 19:25:28,Chris Porritt from Aston Martin just joined as head of vehicle engineering at Tesla,en,107,15,1,"[['Chris', 'I-PER'], ['Porritt', 'I-PER'], ['Aston', 'I-ORG'], ['Martin', 'I-ORG'], ['Tesla', 'I-ORG']]",pos,neu
2013-05-06 19:13:07,"Yup, it is super far. Moon is basically in our back yard relative to Mars.",en,80,16,2,"[['Moon', 'I-LOC'], ['Mars', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2013-05-05 16:27:53,"Definitely a lot of potential for geothermal, but depends on well depth. Too expensive in most places.",en,115,18,2,[],neg,pos
2013-05-05 03:20:17,"Yeah, that probably makes sense.",en,46,6,1,[],pos,pos
2013-05-05 02:51:06,Most people have never heard of Nikola Tesla. have will hopefully change over time.,en,112,16,2,"[['Nikola', 'I-PER'], ['Tesla', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2013-05-05 02:21:47,"yes, that has been the goal from the beginning",en,71,11,1,[],pos,pos
2013-05-04 15:38:53,"It can definitely strain relationships, but Elon Musk loved doing my first company with my's brother",en,103,16,1,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2013-05-04 15:37:59,Norway rocks!,en,26,3,1,"[['Norway', 'I-LOC']]",pos,neu
2013-05-04 06:38:21,"Earnings call next week, then Supercharger week after and then... the mystery announcement/demonstration :)",en,120,15,1,[],neg,pos
2013-05-04 06:37:16,you're welcome :),en,28,4,1,[],pos,pos
2013-05-03 20:55:52,we need a compelling video that convinces TX lawmakers to pass the direct sales law just approved by TX lawmakers's committee.,en,130,21,1,"[['TX', 'I-LOC'], ['TX', 'I-LOC']]",pos,pos
2013-05-03 20:53:08,Guaranteeing the world's best resale value in industry is unprecedented and backed up my other assets. Why isn't Guaranteeing good?,en,140,21,2,[],pos,pos
2013-05-03 20:47:24,"Chris is great. Took a long time for Elon Musk to find someone w truly hardcore engineering skills, who fully understood the system.",en,139,23,2,"[['Chris', 'I-PER'], ['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2013-05-03 19:28:10,Am getting lots of questions about the big Supercharger announcement. Aiming to do that the week after next.,en,108,18,2,"[['Supercharger', 'I-MISC']]",pos,neu
2013-05-03 19:06:04,"Yes, this does put an indirect floor on resale value. Should help all owners.",en,92,15,2,[],pos,pos
2013-05-03 19:00:21,Tesla raises Model S resale value guarantee to highest in auto industry,en,95,13,1,"[['Tesla', 'I-ORG'], ['Model', 'I-MISC'], ['S', 'I-MISC']]",pos,pos
2013-05-03 18:55:36,Side boosters fall short center core goes too far + Florida is heavily populated. Landing permission tricky :),en,124,20,2,"[['Florida', 'I-LOC']]",neg,pos
2013-05-03 18:52:58,"We can't formally provide a guarantee w/o restating accounting, but Elon Musk feel confident about the value anyway.",en,119,18,1,"[['Elon', 'I-PER'], ['Musk', 'I-PER']]",pos,pos
2013-05-03 18:50:54,"Yeah, that is super tricky. Will have to sacrifice a lot of payload to boost back or land on ocean platform.",en,117,22,2,[],neg,pos
2013-05-03 18:24:48,"Yes, your article (and many others) rightly identified that we made a mistake. New financing is not perfect, but much better.",en,136,22,2,[],neg,pos
2013-05-03 16:55:22,"The legs are nested tight against the body of the rocket in flight, so rotate about 120 degrees to deploy",en,118,21,1,[],neg,neu
2013-05-03 08:43:12,More likely that pigs will fly over the frozen wastes of Hell. Clarkson doesn't understand technology.,en,115,17,2,"[['Hell', 'I-LOC'], ['Clarkson', 'I-PER']]",neg,neg
2013-05-03 08:41:24,We did a ton of testing until they could handle 4X legally required impact energy. Extremely tough.,en,112,18,2,[],neg,pos
